<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	
	>
<channel>
	<title>Comments on: What You Resist Persists</title>
	<atom:link href="http://www.andremonserrat.com/2007/12/02/what-you-resist-persists/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2007/12/02/what-you-resist-persists/</link>
	<description>Scattered pages from an apocryphal diary</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 12:42:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.9</generator>
	<item>
		<title>By: Monica</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2007/12/02/what-you-resist-persists/#comment-282</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Monica]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2007 15:42:18 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/2007/12/02/what-you-resist-persists/#comment-282</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[My dear, if you only knew how alone you weren&#039;t with this, it might feel much easier to be able to say out loud.  Everyone lives in shades of this type of gray, and no one goes forever without some sort of shadow across their face.  It&#039;s the only way to ever be able to live in direct sunlight.

But I am proud of you for saying it:)  Closets are so very dark and stuffy, after all!

I had to click on the &quot;key words&quot; section because I had to see that, yes, in fact you had gone back through and labeled the breadcrumbs:) for those in your studio audience.  

I think that part of the problem about speaking about such things is that people try not to believe that they live in such a bizarre, strange, and wonderful world as they do... it&#039;s damn uncomfortable.  And sometimes, it&#039;s terrifying.  And I often feel like there is some &quot;outerly&quot; imposed weight, a barrier maybe, that requires a certain amount of energy to push through in order to speak out loud about such things.

Ah, well.  Fred is right.  You are loved, no matter what.

Enjoy the sunshine...]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>My dear, if you only knew how alone you weren&#8217;t with this, it might feel much easier to be able to say out loud.  Everyone lives in shades of this type of gray, and no one goes forever without some sort of shadow across their face.  It&#8217;s the only way to ever be able to live in direct sunlight.</p>
<p>But I am proud of you for saying it:)  Closets are so very dark and stuffy, after all!</p>
<p>I had to click on the &#8220;key words&#8221; section because I had to see that, yes, in fact you had gone back through and labeled the breadcrumbs:) for those in your studio audience.  </p>
<p>I think that part of the problem about speaking about such things is that people try not to believe that they live in such a bizarre, strange, and wonderful world as they do&#8230; it&#8217;s damn uncomfortable.  And sometimes, it&#8217;s terrifying.  And I often feel like there is some &#8220;outerly&#8221; imposed weight, a barrier maybe, that requires a certain amount of energy to push through in order to speak out loud about such things.</p>
<p>Ah, well.  Fred is right.  You are loved, no matter what.</p>
<p>Enjoy the sunshine&#8230;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>By: Fred</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2007/12/02/what-you-resist-persists/#comment-281</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Fred]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2007 14:37:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/2007/12/02/what-you-resist-persists/#comment-281</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Drey,

No one can live your life for you. Whatever issues you may have, they are your issues and you should take them as part of being who you are.

If &quot;coming out of the closet&quot; makes you a more complete person, by letting out your true feelings about something, then the people who love you shall love you more for having the courage to be honest with them.

Love,

Dad.]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Drey,</p>
<p>No one can live your life for you. Whatever issues you may have, they are your issues and you should take them as part of being who you are.</p>
<p>If &#8220;coming out of the closet&#8221; makes you a more complete person, by letting out your true feelings about something, then the people who love you shall love you more for having the courage to be honest with them.</p>
<p>Love,</p>
<p>Dad.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
