<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>House of Whack &#8211; First Time Flowing</title>
	<atom:link href="http://www.andremonserrat.com/category/creations/house-of-whack-creations/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com</link>
	<description>Scattered pages from an apocryphal diary</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 00:04:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.9</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Out of Focus Much Too Bright</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2011/06/04/out-of-focus-much-too-bright/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2011/06/04/out-of-focus-much-too-bright/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2011 23:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Artwork]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Board Games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[House of Whack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[oneaday]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://andremonserrat.dreynet.com/?p=2810</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I remember when I was working on House of Whack I could just sit there and create graphics for ten hours at a time. And I didn&#8217;t feel it. Time just blew past. Lately I&#8217;ve been noticing that it is hard to stay focused on any one thing, be it a job at work, a [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I remember when I was working on House of Whack I could just sit there and create graphics for ten hours at a time. And I didn&#8217;t feel it. Time just blew past. Lately I&#8217;ve been noticing that it is hard to stay focused on any one thing, be it a job at work, a personal project, video games, TV shows, whatever. Part of it is an energy thing. I&#8217;m tired and unmotivated much of the time. After sitting at a computer for eight hours at work, it is a tough sell to tell myself &#8220;Okay, now it is time to be creative! Let&#8217;s sit in front of the computer some more!&#8221;</p>
<p>Another part of it is I feel like I&#8217;ve got to get it all done, see it all, play it all, before&#8230;what? Before I die? Before I&#8217;m in a relationship? I don&#8217;t know. So, unconsciously, I was becoming very results oriented, wanting to get to the end as quickly as possible. I really need to relax and enjoy the process of whatever I&#8217;m doing.</p>
<p>I&#8217;ve been learning some new software so I can create illustrations of the characters for the Dune game. Learning digital tools is like learning new spells. I want to be able to summon the floating palace right away, but first I need to learn how to push little stone blocks around. My mind cracks open with the possibilities and then is daunted by all there is to learn. There&#8217;s already so much information in my head.</p>
<p>Ugh, even finishing this post is getting to be a struggle. Sleepy sleepy&#8230;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2011/06/04/out-of-focus-much-too-bright/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>3</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>DreyNet 3.0</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2011/05/29/dreynet-3-0/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2011/05/29/dreynet-3-0/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 17:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Artwork]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[House of Whack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The Stork]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[oneaday]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://andremonserrat.dreynet.com/?p=2803</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[At least I think it is the third iteration. Maybe it is the fourth. In any case, I have updated the gateway to my small network of web sites. Let&#8217;s take a quick tour. The home page is a rotating gateway to each site. The sites can also be accessed from the main menu. You [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>At least I think it is the third iteration. Maybe it is the fourth. In any case, I have updated the gateway to my small network of web sites. <a title="DreyNet" href="http://www.dreynet.com" target="_blank">Let&#8217;s take a quick tour</a>.</p>
<p>The home page is a rotating gateway to each site. The sites can also be accessed from the main menu. You will also note a link called &#8220;The Latest&#8221;. That&#8217;s where I will display my most recently completed projects (stories, games, videos, etc.). Social media hooks are in full effect with the tweetbox on the right and a &#8220;Follow Me&#8221; tab displaying numerous online destinations to satisfy your cyber-stalking pleasure.</p>
<p>On to the individual sites:</p>
<p><a href="http://www.andremonserrat.com" target="_blank">First Time Flowing</a> &#8211; My blog. No doubt you are familiar with this one.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.dreampunk.com/" target="_blank">DreamPunk Productions</a> &#8211; This is my &#8220;game and story-shaped design&#8221; studio, home of <a href="http://www.whatisthestork.com/" target="_blank">The Stork</a> and <a href="http://www.houseofwhack.net/" target="_blank">House of Whack</a>. Speaking of which, those each have their own site.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.dreynet.com/mediawiki/index.php?title=In_Between" target="_blank">In Between</a> &#8211; This is a wiki I made to keep track of all the worlds and characters I have created over the years. Managing several universes is a challenging task.</p>
<p>There is another somewhat hidden site, which can be discovered by <a href="http://www.andremonserrat.com/category/life/avatar-life/" target="_blank">the person looking for me</a>.</p>
<p>And there we are, back at the start!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2011/05/29/dreynet-3-0/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brief Update</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2011/03/05/brief-update/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2011/03/05/brief-update/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2011 07:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Artwork]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Board Games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[House of Whack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The Stork]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[oneaday]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=2258</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Just a short status report on where various projects stand&#8230; The Stork &#8211; It looks like the payments got processed sooner than expected, so I can potentially have the book printed several weeks sooner. I&#8217;ve completed the special Kickstarter edition of the book. I&#8217;ll give it another once over before sending it to the printer. [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Just a short status report on where various projects stand&#8230;<span id="more-2258"></span></p>
<p>The Stork &#8211; It looks like the payments got processed sooner than expected, so I can potentially have the book printed several weeks sooner. I&#8217;ve completed the special Kickstarter edition of the book. I&#8217;ll give it another once over before sending it to the printer. I will be setting up a more involved web site for The Stork (and probably revamping all of my existing sites as well).</p>
<p>Dune &#8211; I discovered that there are typos that have been present since the original Avalon Hill edition of the game. I have updated the board with the &#8220;real&#8221; locations on Arrakis (Old Gap instead of OH Gap, Plaster Basin instead of Plastic Basin).</p>
<p>Talisman Revised rules &#8211; The play test session went really well and the new rules made the game more fun. Even though it made the game play faster turn by turn, it still took the usual 3 hours to finish the game.</p>
<p>House Mods/Redecorating &#8211; I now have a nice leather-looking storage ottoman to prop my feet up on as well as store Rock Band peripherals. Also, I had a small fire in the kitchen which caused some smoke damage. There is now a bright cobalt comic book-like BLAM shape painted over the ceiling and wall. I also added some more to the House of Whack mural thing I have going on in the kitchen.</p>
<p>Girlfriend &#8211; No measurable progress. I met a really fantastic woman with a fantastic life and house. No idea if she is into me or not. I spent a lot of time over-thinking it.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2011/03/05/brief-update/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>STAPLE!</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/03/06/staple/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/03/06/staple/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 02:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[House of Whack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The Stork]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=2129</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I hadn&#8217;t heard about STAPLE! until last year. Chris Nicholas, a guy I met in improv classes at The New Movement, created and organized it. It is basically a mini convention for indie comic creators, game designers, and artists in general. You can find out more at www.staple-austin.org . I had never been a vendor [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I hadn&#8217;t heard about STAPLE! until last year. Chris Nicholas, a guy I met in improv classes at The New Movement, created and organized it. It is basically a mini convention for indie comic creators, game designers, and artists in general. You can find out more at <a href="http:/www.staple-austin.org">www.staple-austin.org</a> .</p>
<p>I had never been a vendor at a convention, so I didn&#8217;t know what to expect. Chris warned me that STAPLE! kind of spoils vendors for other conventions because it is such a cool experience. He was not wrong. My vague plan was to roll in there with copies of House of Whack and The Stork and see what happened.<span id="more-2129"></span></p>
<p>Before I left home, I created a little hand drawn sign which had the prices on it. Under The Stork I thought about adding the phrase &#8220;It Will Alter Your Life&#8221;, but then thought it was silly and hyperbolic. But, of course, that was the Cuckoo trying to thwart me. So I went ahead and wrote it in red. I think it made all the difference because I ended up selling 30 copies.</p>
<p>I didn&#8217;t have a fancy sign like a lot of the other vendors. I didn&#8217;t even have a table cloth. Apparently that didn&#8217;t matter in the end. I set up a demo of House of Whack and a pile of The Stork and my little sign. To my left was Big Head Press with graphic novels endorsed by Alan Moore. To my right was David McGuire, the soft spoken creator of the Grastrophobia web comic.</p>
<p>I wasn&#8217;t really sure I could suddenly become a marketing guy who sat at a booth all day, trying to get people to buy my stuff. But I engaged most of the people who walked by, starting conversations with them, giving the elevator pitch for both products. A guy bought House of Whack just because I started talking to him about board games in general. The Stork was the easiest sell of anything I&#8217;ve ever done. For one, it was $1. Secondly, when people grokked what it was about, they bought it, sometimes before I could even finish describing it.</p>
<p>I met all kinds of cool people and made potential contacts. I wasn&#8217;t even trying to network with anyone, but people would just hand me their card and tell me who to talk to in order to get House of Whack in their store.</p>
<p>All in all, it was a fantastic experience.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/03/06/staple/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Achievement Unlocked</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/02/18/achievement-unlocked/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/02/18/achievement-unlocked/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2010 01:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Artwork]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Board Games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[House of Whack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Something Real]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Video Games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Work]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=2092</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Sometimes I fall into that slough of self-examination where I feel as though I have accomplished nothing with my life. Or, when compared to Person X, I am found wanting. This often happens when I&#8217;m not currently working on a creative project, as they tend to define me and give me purpose. So I think [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sometimes I fall into that slough of self-examination where I feel as though I have accomplished nothing with my life. Or, when compared to Person X, I am found wanting. This often happens when I&#8217;m not currently working on a creative project, as they tend to define me and give me purpose.</p>
<p>So I think it might be helpful to recollect the things I <em>have</em> achieved. Not in a boastful, resting on my laurels sort of way. But to remind myself that I am the same person who did all of those things. Try it yourself when you are feeling somewhat less than.<span id="more-2092"></span></p>
<p>Here are some of the things I have accomplished so far:</p>
<ol>
<li>Learned to program in BASIC when I was 8 years old</li>
<li>Wrote a computer game when I was 10 and sold one copy</li>
<li>Learned to ride a bike</li>
<li>Learned to play the trombone</li>
<li>Wrote and directed <em>Welcome to the Real World</em> during my senior year of high school</li>
<li>Wrote and performed skits and monologues in front of hundreds of people</li>
<li>Learned to drive a stick shift</li>
<li>Was class Treasurer and class Chaplain</li>
<li>Was a National Merit Scholar</li>
<li>Read the entire Bible</li>
<li>Graduated high school</li>
<li>Won best supporting actor for my performance in <em>Off Kennedy&#8217;s Yacht</em></li>
<li>Won best playwright for <em>All We See and Seem</em></li>
<li>Helped make the short film <em>K</em></li>
<li>Wrote a thesis on Interactive Fiction</li>
<li>Ran a massively multiplayer interactive fiction game as my senior writing project in college</li>
<li>Saw Pink Floyd in concert</li>
<li>Drove across the U.S. both East to West and North to South</li>
<li>Learned how to build my own computer</li>
<li>Filmed, directed and edited the documentary <em>Goodbye, Hello</em></li>
<li>Graduated college</li>
<li>Survived six car accidents, unscathed</li>
<li>Convinced someone to marry me</li>
<li>Created presentations for the biggest company on earth</li>
<li>Owned a house</li>
<li>Survived a divorce</li>
<li>Taught myself Photoshop, Dreamweaver, Flash, Poser, Illustrator, Premiere, and After Effects</li>
<li>Won a short fiction contest with my story <em>The Numbers Game</em></li>
<li>Published a chapbook of poetry called <em>Poem-Shaped Lies</em></li>
<li>Solved <em>Myst III</em> without any hints</li>
<li>Adapted <em>The Warlock of Firetop Mountain</em> into a module for Neverwinter Nights. It won a contest created by the publishers of the book. (The British) Steve Jackson played it and wrote me a letter of congratulations.</li>
<li>Checked in to a mental institution</li>
<li>Checked out of a mental institution</li>
<li>Made love to beautiful women</li>
<li>Stood naked on top of a volcano</li>
<li>Adopted a pregnant cat</li>
<li>Won a Telly award for my piece on the New Mexico Jazz Workshop</li>
<li>Had a crisis of faith</li>
<li>Learned how to break up with girls</li>
<li>Dual-wielded .45mm pistols</li>
<li>Published another chapbook of poetry called <em>From the Ashes of Puppets</em></li>
<li>Won a fiction contest with my story <em>My Strychnine Valentine</em></li>
<li>Sued the DEA and won</li>
<li>Learned how to make friends in a new city</li>
<li>Lived in at least 9 different cities</li>
<li>Performed slam poetry in five major cities</li>
<li>Created and published a board game called <em>House of Whack</em></li>
<li>Created a web comic called <em>Dream Job</em></li>
<li>Held my own with John Hodgman</li>
<li>Was a guest columnist for Secure Immaturity</li>
<li>Created and organized a film festival for women filmmakers called <em>Something Real</em></li>
<li>Learned how to practice authenticity and integrity</li>
<li>Helped create a bumper for Fantastic Fest called <em>Lollipop</em></li>
<li>Created a board game and beer meetup called <em>Boards &#8216;N Brews</em></li>
<li>Performed improv comedy</li>
<li>Had an existential crisis</li>
<li>Beat Mischa in Wiz-War</li>
<li>Published <em>The Stork</em></li>
<li>Filed my taxes in January</li>
<li>Saw the last night launch of a space shuttle</li>
<li>Designed hundreds of web sites</li>
<li>Avoided ever breaking any bones in my body</li>
<li>Have, at one time or another, lost everything I thought I needed to survive</li>
<li>Did what was right instead of what was easy</li>
</ol>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/02/18/achievement-unlocked/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>The House always wins</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/01/26/the-house-always-wins/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/01/26/the-house-always-wins/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2010 04:21:54 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Board Games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[House of Whack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[What I Did Today]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=2032</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Tonight I brought House of Whack to Boards &#8216;n Brews. It was good to see it on the table again. I hadn&#8217;t taught the game to new players in ages, but this was the smoothest explanation so far. There were four players, a really good size group for newcomers. We played the straight up &#8220;Inside [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tonight I brought House of Whack to Boards &#8216;n Brews. It was good to see it on the table again. I hadn&#8217;t taught the game to new players in ages, but this was the smoothest explanation so far. There were four players, a really good size group for newcomers. We played the straight up &#8220;Inside the Box&#8221; version with nothing fancy. The Throne of Swift and Whimsical Judgment came into play and there was a pretty amusing trial as a result. Dan had a legitimate beef with Jeff, namely being forced to stand while playing and walk around in a circle. The jury was split and it came down to a roll off, which Jeff won. That&#8217;s how it goes down sometimes.</p>
<p>Jeff pulled ahead of everyone on the score track and took home a copy of the game. Good times!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/01/26/the-house-always-wins/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>That is Whack</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2009/02/24/that-is-whack/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2009/02/24/that-is-whack/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2009 01:38:45 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[House of Whack]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=1695</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Ah, here is an appropriate use of a blog: venting. I received an email today that just sent me over the edge of bewilderment and anger. It was from someone I hadn&#8217;t heard from in over a year. The message simply said &#8220;Can you afford to begin paying for my contributions to our game yet?&#8221; [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ah, here is an appropriate use of a blog: venting.</p>
<p>I received an email today that just sent me over the edge of bewilderment and anger. It was from someone I hadn&#8217;t heard from in over a year. The message simply said &#8220;Can you afford to begin paying for my contributions to our game yet?&#8221; And he&#8217;s talking about House of Whack.<span id="more-1695"></span></p>
<p>Just to contextualize, I had started working on the game a few years before I met this guy. He was really interested in it and helped playtest it extensively. We talked about ideas for the game, some of his ideas found their way into the game, most did not. He contributed a few pieces of art for 3 or so cards, which he was credited for. But at no point was there <em>ever </em>an agreement that he would be financially compensated for playtesting. In fact, he explicitly said he just wanted to help out and wasn&#8217;t interested in money. There was no contract or legally binding agreement stating he had any stake or co-ownership of the game. I am very grateful for his support and enthusiasm for the game and I say as much in the credits of the manual.</p>
<p>But it was never &#8220;our&#8221; game and that&#8217;s what infuriates me about his email. It was <em>my </em>idea. I made every single prototype card (hundreds and hundreds of them) through every iteration of the game. I did all of the graphic design and 99% of the original artwork. I created the game mechanics. I wrote and re-wrote the rules countless times. I put <em>thousands </em>of dollars of my own money into the production of the game. I put years of life into making House of Whack happen.</p>
<p>How much time and resources did he contribute to the artwork? Virtually none. He contributed pre-existing photos which I then incorporated into the card design. He did not invent any game mechanics, he wrote no rules, he invested no money. He <em>did </em>come up with some <em>ideas </em>for cards. Yet he feels that in comparison to my contribution to the game, that he can go ahead and refer to it as &#8220;our&#8221; game and ask for compensation.</p>
<p>Here&#8217;s a real example of how this collaboration worked. One day he said, &#8220;It would be cool if there were a labyrinth in the game.&#8221; I agreed. So I thought about a way to create that. I designed graphics for the rooms, mocked up the cards, came up with game mechanics and playtested them. This ended up becoming the Hedge Maze in the game. I then showed him the finished product. He said, &#8220;That was a really cool collaboration we just had.&#8221; In his mind, his making a statement about a labyrinth was somehow equivalent to all the work I did to make it a reality.</p>
<p>He had zero game design sense, no conception of balancing mechanics, and would come up with utterly impractical and nonsensical ideas, even for House of Whack. Once we were tossing around ideas for a play variant involving ghosts. I wanted to call the ghosts &#8220;revenants&#8221; as they were seeking vengeance. He wanted to call them &#8220;detectives&#8221;. I suggested that the word &#8220;detectives&#8221; might be confusing as people generally have a particular idea of what a detective is and they won&#8217;t necessarily associate &#8220;detective&#8221; with &#8220;ghost&#8221;. His response was that, since it was the House of Whack, things are not as they seem, and, in this world, &#8220;detective&#8221; was synonymous with &#8220;ghost&#8221;. His idea was that when a player got killed they would come back as a ghost and have to solve the mystery of who killed them. I said it would be kind of obvious as the player was right there when it happened. He said the player would have to <em>pretend they didn&#8217;t know</em> who the killer was and conduct an investigation. That&#8217;s fucking nonsense.</p>
<p>And so is this &#8220;our game&#8221; bullshit. I had LOTS of people help with the game and I feel like I have acknowledged them all appropriately. But none of them would ever suggest that they put enough work into it to call it their own creation, much less ask me to retroactively pay them for <em>volunteering</em>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2009/02/24/that-is-whack/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>House of Whack Now Available at Indie Press Revolution!</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/10/09/house-of-whack-now-available-at-indie-press-revolution/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/10/09/house-of-whack-now-available-at-indie-press-revolution/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2008 23:07:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[House of Whack]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=803</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[It is an honor to have House of Whack distributed alongside some of the most innovative and important independent role-playing games ever conceived. House of Whack really is a gateway drug to story games and other out of the box gaming experiments, so it really seems like a good fit. Support independent game design at [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It is an honor to have <a href="http://www.houseofwhack.net">House of Whack</a> distributed alongside some of the most innovative and  important independent role-playing games ever conceived. <a href="http://www.houseofwhack.net">House of Whack</a> really is a gateway drug to story games and other out of the box gaming experiments, so it really seems like a good fit.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.indiepressrevolution.com/xcart/home.php">Support independent game design at Indie Press Revolution.</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/10/09/house-of-whack-now-available-at-indie-press-revolution/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>3</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Open Source is Love</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/01/03/open-source-is-love/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/01/03/open-source-is-love/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 05:57:32 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[House of Whack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Activity Report]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/01/03/open-source-is-love/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I&#8217;ve been learning how to create web sites using Joomla!, an open source content management system. This is primarily for work, but I can envision converting the DreamPunk site over to Joomla! at some point. Additionally, I have upgraded the House of Whack forums to the latest version of phpBB, an open source forum. What [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;ve been learning how to create web sites using Joomla!, an open source content management system. This is primarily for work, but I can envision converting the DreamPunk site over to Joomla! at some point.</p>
<p>Additionally, I have upgraded the <a href="http://forum.houseofwhack.net/">House of Whack forums</a> to the latest version of phpBB, an open source forum.</p>
<p>What I need to do next is learn how to make custom templates for both of these packages. Give it that personal touch.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/01/03/open-source-is-love/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Whack Magnets</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/01/02/whack-magnets/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/01/02/whack-magnets/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2008 00:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[House of Whack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Activity Report]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/01/02/whack-magnets/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[A few months ago I ordered some printable magnet material and today I used it to print out a set of rooms from House of Whack. Now I can play on the front of my refrigerator.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A few months ago I ordered some printable magnet material and today I used it to print out a set of rooms from <a href="http://www.houseofwhack.net">House of Whack</a>. Now I can play on the front of my refrigerator.</p>
<p><img src="http://www.andremonserrat.com/files/2011/03/HowFridge.jpg" alt="" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/01/02/whack-magnets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
