<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>CVCA &#8211; First Time Flowing</title>
	<atom:link href="http://www.andremonserrat.com/tag/cvca/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com</link>
	<description>Scattered pages from an apocryphal diary</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 00:04:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.9</generator>
	<item>
		<title>A Window on the Soul</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1990/10/26/a-window-on-the-soul/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1990/10/26/a-window-on-the-soul/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 1990 18:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Geek]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CVCA]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=1819</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[People are like churches: their stained glass windows sparkle and shine when the sun is out, but when the darkness sets in, their true beauty is revealed only if there is a light within.  A weary traveler, worn with the stains of a long journey, has come in search of refuge for the night.  From [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>People are like churches: their stained glass windows sparkle and shine when the sun is out, but when the darkness sets in, their true beauty is revealed only if there is a light within.  A weary traveler, worn with the stains of a long journey, has come in search of refuge for the night.  From the road he sees two churches perched atop two hills.  Both seem immaculately designed, stained glass windows catching the sunlight like diamond facets.  Either appears as a comfortable place which would welcome wayfarers such as he.  Choosing the nearest one, he wanders up the hill and enters in.<span id="more-1819"></span></p>
<p>Several hours pass and a fierce storm blows in from the west, roiling black clouds blotting out the light, casting all into shadows.  The keepers of one church, afraid of the storm, flee the building for want of more protection.  From the windows of the other church, a light beams out, for its faithful keepers have remained to wait out the tempest. Travelers coming from afar see a beacon of light in the darkness, beckoning them on to sanctuary.<br />
As they near the hill, they see the church with its beautiful windows and breathe a sigh of<br />
relief.  They pass by the other church; the darkness enshrouds it so much that it might as well not have been there in the first place.</p>
<p>Christians are comparable to a church with stained glass windows.  On the outside, a person<br />
may profess Christianity and for all intents and purposes, he appears as one.  One person may have a very good Christian act while another one is a genuine Christian.  The light of Christ shines within true Christians and it takes a test or a trial to reveal that light.  When the<br />
Enemy attacks, the true Christians will remain standing as models of faith while the charlatans flee or fold under the attack.  When it comes down to doing some serious things for God, like the darkened church, if a person does not plan to live up to the name &#8220;Christian&#8221; then he might as well not become one.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1990/10/26/a-window-on-the-soul/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chapter 2</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1990/01/31/chapter-2/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1990/01/31/chapter-2/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 1990 18:22:15 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Reft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CVCA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grey]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=1824</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[&#8220;What is the symbolism in the spider?&#8221; asked the girl. Grey looked up from where he was sitting on the floor of the apartment. &#8220;What?!&#8221; he asked, puzzled and shocked. &#8220;Does the spider has some hidden meaning to it?&#8221; she elaborated. &#8220;I mean, everything else always has: the Iron Tower, the chasms, you know.&#8221; &#8220;That [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;What is the symbolism in the spider?&#8221; asked the girl.<br />
Grey looked up from where he was sitting on the floor of the apartment.<br />
&#8220;What?!&#8221; he asked, puzzled and shocked.<br />
&#8220;Does the spider has some hidden meaning to it?&#8221; she elaborated. &#8220;I mean,<br />
everything else always has: the Iron Tower, the chasms, you know.&#8221;<br />
&#8220;That was a different place and a different time,&#8221; explained Grey. &#8220;The<br />
only significance of the spider is that it really freaked me out, that&#8217;s all.<br />
Why do you always have to be looking for &#8216;hidden meanings&#8217; and &#8216;deep sig<br />
nificance&#8217; im every little thing?&#8221;<br />
&#8220;Sorry,&#8221; she apologized insincerely. &#8220;I guess I&#8217;m just so used to it!&#8221;<br />
Grey endured a few seconds of her scornful gaze before looking away. He<br />
scanned the apartment again. Nothing much here; ruined furniture, the window<br />
they came in and the door leading out. They would probably go through the door<br />
pretty soon.<br />
&#8220;Grey,&#8221; she said. &#8220;Why did you bring me along with you?&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1990/01/31/chapter-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chapter 1</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1990/01/29/chapter-1/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1990/01/29/chapter-1/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 1990 18:19:01 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Reft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CVCA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grey]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=1822</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Hey, here is the story Forget about the trouble in life Don&#8217;t you know it&#8217;s not easy When you gotta walk upon that line A dark alley where only shadows chose to dwell&#8230; Scraps of paper and assorted refuse blew about on the gusty winds. Several rats foraged for sustenance in others&#8217; discarded waste. The [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Hey, here is the story<br />
Forget about the trouble in life<br />
Don&#8217;t you know it&#8217;s not easy<br />
When you gotta walk upon that line</em></p>
<p>A dark alley where only shadows chose to dwell&#8230;<br />
Scraps of paper and assorted refuse blew about on the gusty winds. Several<br />
rats foraged for sustenance in others&#8217; discarded waste. The sudden appearance<br />
of a mangy tomcat sent the rats scurrying for their burrows. Licking its paws,<br />
the cat reflected on its loss of a meal.<br />
A brilliant blue line of light cut across the fabric of reality in that<br />
back alley. The line hovered above the ground for a few moments before expand<br />
ing upward into a glowing rectangular portal.<br />
And two came through from the other side&#8230;</p>
<p>The cat screeched at the appearance of the boy and the girl and then ran at<br />
full speed to safer hunting grounds.<br />
The boy wrapped his trenchcoat closer to his body as the air was much<br />
cooler here. The girl stood staring at their surroundings, taking in this new<br />
scene. She had seen many wonders in the other place, and it was strange for<br />
her to see something that could be called anything close to normal or sane.<br />
Her gaze returned the boy and found that he looked a little different than<br />
before; he had changed again.<br />
&#8220;Who are you this time?&#8221; she asked nonchalantly.<br />
&#8220;Name&#8217;s Grey.&#8221; he replied with a smirk.<br />
&#8220;Why are you called &#8216;Grey&#8217; here?&#8221;<br />
&#8220;Because I am.&#8221; he answered simply, offering no explanation. The girl<br />
decided to leave it at that and move on to another topic.<br />
&#8220;How come you change and I don&#8217;t?&#8221;<br />
&#8220;Who says you haven&#8217;t changed?&#8221; he said. &#8220;You have, but you just didn&#8217;t<br />
notice it.&#8221; His eyes wandered, inspecting the alley.<br />
&#8220;What do you mean&#8230;&#8221; she started to say, but was stopped short as she<br />
caught her reflection in a plane of glass. &#8220;I..I&#8217;m beautiful!&#8221;<br />
&#8220;You&#8217;ve always been beautiful&#8230;&#8221; said Grey.<br />
&#8220;No, I mean, awesome beautiful! I mean, BETTER!&#8221;<br />
&#8220;Yeah, I guess that we are both in an &#8216;ideal state&#8217;.&#8221; Grey stood there,<br />
whistling a soft tune as the girl examined herself up and down. He was rather<br />
annoyed, for he was used to such things and he wanted to get on with every<br />
thing.<br />
But just what was everything? Why were they here, anyway? He had to for<br />
cibly hold down a cold fear that threatened to freeze his heart. He would have<br />
to hide his ignorance from the girl; wouldn&#8217;t want to frighten her.<br />
&#8220;Hey,&#8221; said the girl suddenly. &#8220;Where is she? Didn&#8217;t she come through with<br />
us?&#8221; She looked back at the door, but found only a brick wall. The portal had<br />
closed and vanished.<br />
&#8220;She took a different path, hon.&#8221; Grey explained matter-of-factly.<br />
&#8220;Oh.&#8221; she said, nodding her head. A tinge of regret and sadness chanced to<br />
enter her heart, but was quickly ushered out as an intruder.<br />
&#8220;Take it easy. Don&#8217;t worry about it.&#8221; he said, patting her shoulder, reas<br />
suringly.<br />
She looked up at him and caught his gaze.<br />
&#8220;I&#8217;m fine.&#8221; she assured him in a steel tone.<br />
&#8220;Of course you are.&#8221; He looked away from her and diverted his eyes to a<br />
rusty fire escape above them. &#8220;Let&#8217;s get out of here.&#8221;<br />
&#8220;Where are we going?&#8221; she asked.<br />
&#8220;Up.&#8221; With that, he made a springing leap to the spring-hinged ladder<br />
several feet above. He caught onto it and rode it down until it was fully ex<br />
tended. He clambered up to the landing platform and the ladder folded back up<br />
with a clash.<br />
&#8220;Come on up,&#8221; he said.<br />
&#8220;What?&#8221; she asked, amazed. &#8220;How am I supposed to get up there? I can&#8217;t<br />
jump up there, like you! Really, you ask too much of me, Grey.&#8221;<br />
&#8220;Well fine,&#8221; he replied. &#8220;Just find your own way up.&#8221; He secretly wondered<br />
if he was going to have to help her and whether she would let him.<br />
The girl looked around the dead-end alley and spotted the cluster of gar<br />
bage cans. She walked over to them and dragged the sturdiest one over so that<br />
it was just underneath the ladder. Climbing upon this, she was able to reach<br />
the ladder and climb up.<br />
&#8220;Bravo,&#8221; yawned Grey.<br />
&#8220;Shut up,&#8221; said the girl.</p>
<p>&#8220;I don&#8217;t think we should be in here,&#8221; said the girl, looking around the<br />
dark apartment.<br />
&#8220;Who&#8217;s gonna care?&#8221; asked Grey rhetorically. He kicked at an overturned<br />
table and it fell apart. &#8220;It looks like no one&#8217;s been in here for ages.&#8221;<br />
&#8220;Well I still think you didn&#8217;t need to break the window.&#8221;<br />
&#8220;It was stuck&#8230;&#8221; Glass crunched under his steps as he walked over to the<br />
wall and examined a dusty picture.<br />
&#8220;Eww,&#8221; muttered the girl. &#8220;There&#8217;s a spider on your back.&#8221;<br />
Grey spun around, eyes wild.<br />
&#8220;What? Get it off!!&#8221;<br />
&#8220;Well, I&#8217;m not going to touch it&#8230;&#8221;<br />
&#8220;Aughhh! Get it off meee!&#8221;<br />
The girl watched in amused silence as Grey danced about for a while, swat<br />
ting at his back before taking off his trenchcoat. The large, hairy arachnid<br />
scuttled off of the coat and was crushed by Grey&#8217;s boot.<br />
&#8220;Ugh,&#8221; he said in disgust. &#8220;Damn, I hate spiders.&#8221; He collected his coat,<br />
examining it for any other creatures before putting it back on.<br />
&#8220;What&#8217;s so funny?!&#8221; he demanded, seeing the slight smirk on the girl&#8217;s<br />
face.<br />
&#8220;Nothing,&#8221; she replied, stifling a snicker.</p>
<p>TO BE CONTINUED&#8230;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1990/01/29/chapter-1/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
