<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>dating &#8211; First Time Flowing</title>
	<atom:link href="http://www.andremonserrat.com/tag/dating/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com</link>
	<description>Scattered pages from an apocryphal diary</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 00:04:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.9</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Meetup</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2007/09/12/meetup/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2007/09/12/meetup/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2007 00:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Food]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Movies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Austin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dating]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Landmark]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[movies]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/2007/09/12/meetup/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[One of the first things I did when I got to Austin was to sign up for interesting groups at Meetup.com. I get to meet people with similar interests and check out cool new places in Austin. Right now I&#8217;m part of Discovering Austin, a couple wine/coffee/singles Meetup groups, a sushi group, two Landmark groups, [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the first things I did when I got to Austin was to sign up for interesting groups at <a href="http://www.meetup.com">Meetup.com</a>. I get to meet people with similar interests and check out cool new places in Austin.</p>
<p>Right now I&#8217;m part of Discovering Austin, a couple wine/coffee/singles Meetup groups, a sushi group, two Landmark groups, and two movie groups. One of the movie groups is the Alamo Drafthouse Fans, which I am an assistant organizer for. That means I get to pick movies, schedule events and get people to come to the Alamo to have a good time!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2007/09/12/meetup/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>It&#8217;s Just Lunch</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2007/09/05/its-just-lunch/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2007/09/05/its-just-lunch/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2007 03:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dating]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/2007/09/05/its-just-lunch/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[As a Christmas gift for myself, I had signed up for the &#8220;It&#8217;s Just Lunch&#8221; dating service for busy professionals. I describe the person I am looking for and the company tries to match me up with someone looking for me. They make reservations at a night restaurant for lunch or after work drinks and [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As a Christmas gift for myself, I had signed up for the &#8220;It&#8217;s Just Lunch&#8221; dating service for busy professionals. I describe the person I am looking for and the company tries to match me up with someone looking for me. They make reservations at a night restaurant for lunch or after work drinks and I go on a blind date.</p>
<p>This process enabled me to articulate the sort of woman I enjoy spending time with. I told them I liked quirky, creative types who had a spiritual dimension to them, who were honest and expressive. I stressed that it be made known that I was a big movie geek and enjoyed lots of geeky activities. Potential dates should know what they are in for!</p>
<p>For the most part, the service set me up with really nice women who were pretty. But there was never really a spark and oftentimes they were fairly mainstream. They wanted to talk about what we did for a living, not about life goals and plans or being self-expressive.</p>
<p>Originally, I signed up with the intention of finding someone to date. After moving to Austin, I revised that intention as I now just wanted to meet some new people and get acquainted with the city. I gradually came to terms with the fact that I really wanted to find someone to have a serious relationship. I didn&#8217;t want to casually date anyone. I wanted to create the possibility of a lasting, loving partnership. While I tried to stay open to the possibility of meeting such a person through a dating service, I felt like I wasn&#8217;t going to meet that person in such a way. I thought, &#8220;Maybe the person I&#8217;m attracted to would never use a dating service or they wouldn&#8217;t spend this much money on it.&#8221;</p>
<p>So I became cautiously optimistic, but extremely picky. I can see the value of such a service, but I&#8217;m not sure if it is the right thing for me.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2007/09/05/its-just-lunch/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
