<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Cathy &#8211; First Time Flowing</title>
	<atom:link href="http://www.andremonserrat.com/tag/cathy/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com</link>
	<description>Scattered pages from an apocryphal diary</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 00:04:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.9</generator>
	<item>
		<title>So Dry</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/12/30/so-dry/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/12/30/so-dry/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 14:59:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Dreams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathy]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=901</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I haven&#8217;t had any nightmares that I remembered for quite some time. In last night&#8217;s dream, my ex-wife had decided to return and move in with me. It was nice to see her, but I had moved on in my life and I was trying to think of a way to break the news to [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I haven&#8217;t had any nightmares that I remembered for quite some time. In last night&#8217;s dream, my ex-wife had decided to return and move in with me. It was nice to see her, but I had moved on in my life and I was trying to think of a way to break the news to her that I didn&#8217;t want to be with her. I discussed this with my friends who were saddened by my decision, but also understanding.</p>
<p>I went to the bathroom to take a shower. While looking at myself in the mirror, I noticed that my skin was extremely dry. Marbled veins of dryness covered my body liked cracked earth during a drought. I frantically slathered moisturizing lotion all over me, spreading it on so thick it looked like I had crawled out from a vat of pancake batter. The pressure of this rubbing caused my skin to burst in places, sending heavy streams of blood down my face.</p>
<p>This was too much to handle so I called for my mother, who happened to be at my house at the time. She came into the bathroom and promptly slipped on the floor, falling, hitting her head on the edge of toilet. I carefully turned her around and propped her up. Her eyes were milky and opaque. She was blind.</p>
<p>Then I had some other dream, but this one stuck with me.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/12/30/so-dry/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>3</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>You can stand right there if you want</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/08/10/you-can-stand-right-there-if-you-want/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/08/10/you-can-stand-right-there-if-you-want/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2008 01:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Landmark]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Los Angeles]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=739</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[A few days earlier, Beth had made an oblique reference that she knew where Cathy had ended up. I mentally filed that away, but didn&#8217;t bring it up again. Most of the time I have the context &#8220;Cathy who?&#8221; She doesn&#8217;t come up in the day to day. But there are ordinary objects, places, phrases [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A few days earlier, Beth had made an oblique reference that she knew where Cathy had ended up. I mentally filed that away, but didn&#8217;t bring it up again. Most of the time I have the context &#8220;Cathy who?&#8221; She doesn&#8217;t come up in the day to day. But there are ordinary objects, places, phrases and people which are actually disguised keys that unlock a hidden time period. In this group of friends, the Cathy-shaped gap must be quite prominent for them. I never really thought about it until now. She essentially fell off the face of the planet for seven years. For all of us.<span id="more-739"></span></p>
<p>I was hanging out in the backstage area with Dave&#8217;s wonderful interior designer housemate, discussing relationships and the Landmark Forum (which she was attending that weekend). Beth came in and joined us. I don&#8217;t recall how the conversation took this turn, but suddenly Beth was telling me things about Cathy. I remembered what Beth had said before and I asked if she knew where Cathy had ended up.</p>
<p>I remember her saying that Cathy was married and had a child. I blurted something and fled the room. I had expected her to tell me where she was living. This information was totally unexpected and it fried my brain. A roulette wheel of emotions started cutting into my chest. Whatever I was feeling, I only felt it for a few seconds before it changed into something else. I realized I was no longer backstage and there were people going to a fro. I found myself a doorway suitable for soliloquies and installed myself therein.</p>
<p>It wasn&#8217;t as though I had never considered it. I just never had the thought made real. Given the conversation I just had with the housemate, my heart was in a vulnerable place. It&#8217;s not that I was upset about her being married and having a child; it&#8217;s that my desire for a happy relationship was put into stark relief.</p>
<p>Seven years had passed. Lifetimes for me. But a portion of those years I kept frozen in a phial. Now that icy teardrop melted and flowed free.</p>
<p>I&#8217;m going on.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/08/10/you-can-stand-right-there-if-you-want/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>4</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>My Social Network</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2007/02/24/my-social-network/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2007/02/24/my-social-network/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2007 06:48:48 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Albuquerque]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[college]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jess]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[poetry]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/2007/02/24/my-social-network/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[On a whim, I decided to map out my current social network. It illustrates the chain of circumstances responsible for my current relationships. As you can see, this is all Jodi&#8217;s fault. Click on the image for the full view.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On a whim, I decided to map out my current social network. It illustrates the chain of circumstances responsible for my current relationships.</p>
<p>As you can see, this is all Jodi&#8217;s fault.</p>
<p>Click on the image for the full view.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.andremonserrat.com/files/2011/03/Drey's-Social-Network.gif" title="Drey's Social Network" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.andremonserrat.com/files/2011/03/Drey's-Social-Network-Thumb.gif" /></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2007/02/24/my-social-network/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>I Miss You</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2005/08/21/i-miss-you/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2005/08/21/i-miss-you/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2005 04:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geek]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jess]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://andremonserrat.dreynet.com/2005/08/21/i-miss-you/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[&#8220;Don&#8217;t waste your time on me, you&#8217;re already the voice inside my head.&#8221; I miss everyone tonight. I miss my friends, even if I&#8217;ve just seen them. I miss how some friends were a few weeks ago. I miss girls I should never have kissed. I miss girls I should have but now it&#8217;s too [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Don&#8217;t waste your time on me, you&#8217;re already the voice inside my head.&#8221;</p>
<p>I miss everyone tonight.<br />
I miss my friends, even if I&#8217;ve just seen them.<br />
I miss how some friends were a few weeks ago.<br />
I miss girls I should never have kissed.<br />
I miss girls I should have but now it&#8217;s too late.<br />
I miss my ex-girlfriends.<br />
I miss my lovers.<br />
I miss Cathy.<br />
I miss how my friends were in college.<br />
I miss wine and cheese with Beth.<br />
I miss Neal.<br />
I miss my best friends, separated by distances physical and psychological.<br />
I miss my mom.<br />
I miss my sister and my neices.<br />
I miss my grandmother.<br />
I miss Kevmo and The Airliner.<br />
I miss road trips.<br />
I miss being in love.<br />
I miss church.<br />
I miss God.<br />
I miss the little red haired girl.<br />
I already miss Christopher Eccleston, you fucking heartbreaker.<br />
I miss Buffy.<br />
I miss Serenity.<br />
I miss poetry that isn&#8217;t about fear.<br />
I miss Michael Hutchence.<br />
I miss Dumbledore, JK, you cruel woman.<br />
I miss garage sales.<br />
I miss my Apple II+.<br />
I miss floppy disks.<br />
I miss not needing money.<br />
I miss inventing games in the back of the school bus.<br />
I miss recess.<br />
I miss feeling safe.<br />
I miss not knowing.<br />
I miss the way it used to be.<br />
I miss you.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2005/08/21/i-miss-you/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Photos v.2</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2005/06/23/photos/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2005/06/23/photos/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2005 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[poetry]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://andremonserrat.dreynet.com/2005/06/23/photos/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Here&#8217;s a poem I recently reworked and tightened up a bit. Photos v.2 I spent five years filling up a photo album with a house, a car, a dog, a set of tools, a nice dining room set, and you. And you in your wedding dress And you smiling by the SOLD sign And you [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Here&#8217;s a poem I recently reworked and tightened up a bit.</p>
<p>Photos<br />
v.2</p>
<p>I spent five years filling up a photo album with a house, a car, a dog, a set of tools, a nice dining room set, and you.<br />
And you in your wedding dress<br />
And you smiling by the SOLD sign<br />
And you raking the leaves<br />
And you looking at me like I was forever.<br />
I was an amateur photographer, to be sure<br />
Shooting from the hip<br />
Sending up a prayer that when the camera winked<br />
Something would develop:<br />
Be they happy accidents<br />
The smeared blur of a smile<br />
You on a camel, framed by a pyramid<br />
The montage of a child&#8217;s face, my eyes, your nose<br />
Or the sepia toned hope of you and me wrinkling in a sunset forty years away<br />
But now I wonder<br />
Did someone else borrow my camera for the last five years?<br />
In the economy of betrayal<br />
One word is worth a thousand pictures<br />
&#8220;I do&#8221; bought two thousand moments<br />
&#8220;Divorce&#8221; took half of them back<br />
It&#8217;s an expensive word<br />
It cost a house, a car, a dog, a set of tools, a nice dining room set, and you.<br />
And you packing up your wedding dress<br />
And you putting up a FOR SALE sign<br />
And you leaving the rake<br />
And you looking at me like I never meant anything<br />
And it cost you me.<br />
All those photos, just gone<br />
As though I had spent the last five years taking pictures of the sun.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2005/06/23/photos/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>New House Dream</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2005/04/16/dream/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2005/04/16/dream/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2005 20:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Dreams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathy]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://andremonserrat.dreynet.com/2005/04/16/dream/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[At the end of one dream I was with someone and we were going to go to some kind of children&#8217;s museum. We walked into the door where we thought the museum would be and found that things looked very different from the last time we were there. It looked more like a hospital. As [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>At the end of one dream I was with someone and we were going to go to some kind of children&#8217;s museum. We walked into the door where we thought the museum would be and found that things looked very different from the last time we were there. It looked more like a hospital. As it turned out, we had wandered into the children&#8217;s hospital instead.</p>
<p>I think perhaps the person I was with was my ex-wife Cathy. This segued into the next dream where I had gotten back together with Cathy and we were moving into a new house. I kept wondering where I was going to put all my things. There was already a bed there. I would no longer have my own bedroom and this bothered me. I started wondering if this was what I really wanted. So much had happened in the years since we got divorced and I wasn&#8217;t sure she really knew me any more. I stood in the upstairs living room of the new house (off-white carpet, white walls) and watched a black widow spider come and drag the carcass of a cockroach away. This was the most realistic part of the dream, the one filled with the most detail.</p>
<p>I went to explore the rest of the new house. There was a patio that opened off the kitchen, leading to a forest of very tall trees. Perhaps our new house was in the redwood forest of California. As soon as I set foot into the forest, a small one-man starfighter began a strafing run between the immense trees. I had to run and dodge laser blasts until I was safe in the kitchen. Apparently our new house could withstand laser blasts.</p>
<p>That&#8217;s all.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2005/04/16/dream/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Little Earthquakes</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2003/08/05/little-earthquakes/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2003/08/05/little-earthquakes/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2003 15:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Reft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathy]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=1762</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[For some reason, my alarm didn’t go off this morning even though it was set. {Gee, electrical equipment failing.  That’s a new one.} I actually didn’t feel too bad despite sleeping very little due to the mushrooms. At work, as I was looking for some apartment footage, I came across a box with video from [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For some reason, my alarm didn’t go off this morning even though it was set. <em>{Gee, electrical equipment failing.  That’s a new one.}</em> I actually didn’t feel too bad despite sleeping very little due to the mushrooms.</p>
<p>At work, as I was looking for some apartment footage, I came across a box with video from a friend’s wedding that occurred a couple years ago.  I popped it in and was taken aback to see myself and my ex-wife on the video.  What are the chances that the company I ended up working for would have taped this wedding and held onto the raw footage for no reason and placed it where it didn’t belong?  I guess I had about two tears left for Cathy.  It was just kind of a shock.  The tapes ended up in the “to be erased” box.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2003/08/05/little-earthquakes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>This is a Story No One Else Has Read</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2003/06/19/this-is-a-story-no-one-else-has-read/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2003/06/19/this-is-a-story-no-one-else-has-read/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2003 14:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Geek]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jess]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[non serviam]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[reft]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=1734</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[It transpires like this: My wife, Cathy, whom I have been married to for x number of years (x = heart memory, buried memory, misty and unaccounted for. The lost time blows over the plain of my inner world, leaving shadows like gaping mouths rolling ever closer.) decides that enough’s enough. She quit her job, [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It transpires like this: My wife, Cathy, whom I have been married to for x number of years (x = heart memory, buried memory, misty and unaccounted for. The lost time blows over the plain of my inner world, leaving shadows like gaping mouths rolling ever closer.) decides that enough’s enough. She quit her job, she quit church and when that didn’t make her life better, she quit me.<span id="more-1734"></span><br />
I know Doug because he installed our home alarm system. It was always going off while we were at work and the police visited our house on many occasions to try to catch the ghost who kept triggering it. It may have been our dog, Frodo, or it may have been a warning, a dispatch from the universe to find a bomb shelter. So one day Doug comes in to where I work to set up the alarm system there. He’s heard about the divorce thing and he invites me to go out with him and his girlfriend to a bar. I’m not really a bar kind of guy. I’m not sure what kind of guy I am at the time and I guess I seize on this moment of flux and decide that from now on my life will be different. So I say “yeah.”</p>
<p>Doug lives a few blocks from the small kingdom I have been exiled from, namely our house. He has an arcade and a surveillance system. I meet a bunch of people and immediately forget their names. One couple is divorced, but they are trying to date each other again. This is meant to give me hope. Part of me is already waking up. Part of me is insane with glee that I am free again. I don’t want that kind of hope. Not anymore.</p>
<p>We go to this dive called “Misty’s Hideaway” and I can tell it’s somewhere I would never have decided to venture into on my own. I decide that if I have a beer and a pack of cigarettes, I’ll be fine. I’ll have something to do with my hands and something to put in my mouth when the inevitable uncomfortable silence arrives. I sit with them at a back table and begin to study the crowd. So it’s come to this, I think.</p>
<p>But then I see you talking to this guy who looks like he walked out of an article in Rolling Stone, circa 1986, during the hair metal era. I have no idea who you are, but I’m transfixed. I’m already jealous of this guy. I’m already hoping you’ll blow him off. Impossibly, you eventually stop listening to him tell you about a dream and you walk over to our table, into my dream.</p>
<p>Somehow you know the people I am with. You start talking to me. I have no idea what was said. I decide that you’re out of my league and don’t try to impress you and instead just talk to you like a normal person. I may have bummed a few cigarettes from you. I can’t believe how beautiful your eyes are, so I look at my drink or the ashtray or a mark on the table instead of staring.</p>
<p>I watch you dance and it is the most terrifying sight I have ever seen. I am not ready to move through a world that shimmers in a heat haze generated by your gyrations. My heart is gathering itself from a hundred blasted bits and it cannot deal with such beauty.</p>
<p>Doug is having an after hours party and I make sure you know you’re invited. I fear that you won’t come. I fear that you will come. Doug notices my interest and wonders aloud if he should tell you that I want to “take you home and fuck your brains out.” I decide not to tear his throat out.</p>
<p>You do show up at his house. You remember me from the bar. You mingle about the crowded house as though you know everyone. I listen to everything you say. You talk about white water rafting on the Colorado River. Everything you say is an adventure.<br />
When you leave I mutter something about hoping to run into you again. You hand me your phone number. I couldn’t believe it. It was like someone handed me a map to Narnia.</p>
<p>I will always be mindful of the interconnectedness of things. I will always see you for the first time.</p>
<p>We meet for lunch for the first time at Woody’s, some café a short distance from where I work. On the phone I am so excited and nervous that all the street names rearrange themselves on my map and fictitious intersections spill out of my babbling mouth.</p>
<p>As we talk at lunch, I wonder if I should say anything about the divorce and potentially ruin my chances with you. I decide not to put any spin on my answers and answer your questions completely and honestly.</p>
<p>I will always tell you the truth.</p>
<p>I am at a barbeque with the other members of my church small group, talking to Pastor Alan as he grills burgers. This man once had a demon attached to him while he was still a pastor. He was asked to leave our church because he believed in demons and the supernatural and all sorts of “crazy” things. He left to start his own church and I followed him.</p>
<p>I tell him about you and he warns me not to become involved with you. He fears that because of my compassionate heart I will become entangled in your life and try to rescue you somehow.</p>
<p>I nod and completely ignore his advice.</p>
<p>I will try to follow my heart, even if it contradicts the wisdom of men.</p>
<p>You’re stretched across the couch in my apartment in the heights, intoxicatingly beautiful. We’re having a wonderful discussion/argument. You’re saying things that part of me has always known to be true, yet I am arguing against you. It has been a long time since I’ve had such a stimulating conversation. Cathy would always get mad whenever we had a “debate.” She thought I was trying to prove that I was smarter than she. I was just exploring a topic, trying to understand it from different angles. This method rarely goes over well with most people, including you. Everyone always thinks I am advocating a point of view when I am actually exploring a line of reasoning objectively.</p>
<p>You’re trying to convince me that the people in my stories are real, existing in another dimension of possibility. I insist this is quite impossible. I am forgetting the long conversations I used to have with imaginary mice and dragons in my bedroom growing up. The group of very ordinary children I would visit in a completely invented thoughtspace. The wispy dark creatures with glowing eyes, uncoiling from the ceiling, skittering about the furniture. I invited them into my house and they never left.</p>
<p>Your opinions, thoughts and beliefs are precious to me.<br />
The fact that you speak what is true is more important than whether or not I agree.</p>
<p>You have invited me to come over to have brunch with you and your children. I am nervous about meeting them. What if they don’t like me? What if they think I am an intruder? What if they generation gap me and make me feel old? I enter your house for the first time and they are all looking at me. I forget their names and who is older than whom.</p>
<p>You show me your artwork and I am very impressed and at a loss for words. I feel like anything I say would be stupid and ignorant. I try to convey my lack of understanding and un-connectedness with your artwork, but it comes out all wrong.</p>
<p>I get the tour of the house and see your bedroom. It is one of the most inviting and sensual places I had ever been in. I guess that I would probably never see it again.</p>
<p>I love your family and your home and I know that they are not mine.</p>
<p>I will always be grateful to you for sharing them with me, though there is nothing I could do to deserve them.</p>
<p>We are at an event out in the desert where they have the 3-sided hole. Aaron is with us. I am dating Amy and our relationship is at its platonic zenith. I see you as a beautiful woman who am friends with, someone I care deeply about. I look forward to our cigarettes and glasses of wine out on your porch. This is who we are. A week ago I was talking to Jodi on the phone and talking about going to this event. She teased me about maybe you and I could snuggle together in a sleeping blanket. I explained that it wasn’t like that; we were just friends. Besides, there was Amy.</p>
<p>I faced the evening with a bit of guardedness. This gathering had all the trappings of some kind of pagan shenanigans and I wasn’t sure what to think about it. But by end of the evening I was covered in glitter, my feet washed, my head anointed with frankincense, I was wearing a sarong and tripping on mushrooms.</p>
<p>And you were dancing, dancing, spinning and bending. A flame, a dream, a shadow, a reed, the invisible flow of life energy.</p>
<p>I want to know and love each of your changing shapes.</p>
<p>A tale from folklore:</p>
<p>A boy began to climb a mountain.<br />
Halfway up, he encountered a snake coiled in the shadows of a rock.<br />
“Little boy,” hissed the snake. “Winter is coming and if I do not make it over to the other side of the mountain, I will freeze to death. Please put me in your pack and carry me with you to the other side.”<br />
The boy immediately replied,<br />
“But you are a snake. Snakes bite little boys.”<br />
“No,” said the snake, “I will not bite you. If I did, you would die and then there would be no one to carry me over the mountain.”<br />
The boy considered this and it seemed like wisdom. Warily he agreed and slipped the snake into the pack on his back. Together they journeyed up and over the mountain.<br />
When they reached the other side, the boy took the snake out and said, “There, on this side you will be safe from the winter.”<br />
“Thank you,” said the snake and bit the boy.<br />
“Why did you do that?” the boy cried,<br />
feeling the poison flowing into his body.<br />
“It is in my nature,” said the snake.<br />
“You knew what I was before you picked me up.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2003/06/19/this-is-a-story-no-one-else-has-read/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Small Hands</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2001/12/02/small-hands/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2001/12/02/small-hands/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2001 05:36:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[poetry]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/2001/12/02/small-hands/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[This is the world and I cannot hold it Like a mother holds a child Like a lover holds time I better try grabbing onto the rings of Saturn Before I try to hold a world Spinning fast enough to hold us to the ground Giving our hopes stunted wings Pulling the sand through the [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is the world and I cannot hold it<br />
Like a mother holds a child<br />
Like a lover holds time<br />
I better try grabbing onto the rings of Saturn<br />
Before I try to hold a world<br />
Spinning fast enough to hold us to the ground<br />
Giving our hopes stunted wings<br />
Pulling the sand through the hourglass<br />
With a world spinning so fast you&#8217;d think there&#8217;d be a roaring wind<br />
And there is, but we&#8217;ve got the volume down so low<br />
That mother&#8217;s crying cannot be heard over the rustle of father&#8217;s newspaper<br />
But I hear the wind<br />
It sounds like I&#8217;m jet skiing the slipstream of a 767 en route to the cover of Time Magazine<br />
It sounds like I&#8217;m showering in Niagra Falls, but I never get clean.<br />
Like eyes that can&#8217;t bear to meet.<br />
Like my small hands trying to catch you before you fall.<br />
It sounds like the breath I take before saying &#8220;I think I see God.&#8221;<br />
In college, the cafeteria ladies thought I was Jesus<br />
And made sure I got the hot rolls<br />
But they didn&#8217;t see me that night when I was so drunk<br />
And the door was locked<br />
And she was just right there<br />
And I made such a mistake<br />
I woke up with the room spinning, the world spinning.<br />
My friends and I swaggered through our college lives<br />
Immortal. We would never say good-bye.<br />
But then a wind started to pick up the leaves, our plans, and our time<br />
Into a swirling dance<br />
Our feet were heavy<br />
And our hands were so small<br />
The world spun faster<br />
Through the endless cornfields of Greencastle, Indiana<br />
Through the deceptive peace of Albany, New York<br />
Broken by a ringing phone.<br />
When I answered<br />
I heard a voice, once so calm,<br />
Breaking like old violin strings<br />
as it told me a horrible lie.<br />
Neal, who was beautiful;<br />
Neal, who had composed music from some dream country I could not even look upon,<br />
Had not made it out of the woods<br />
Somewhere he lay pale and still<br />
Bathed in silent white light.<br />
The secret was out:<br />
One of us was mortal<br />
One of us would only live in photographs and &#8220;remember when&#8221;<br />
And I realized that none of us were out of the woods yet.<br />
I&#8217;m knocking on Heaven&#8217;s door<br />
I&#8217;m out here with a list of questions that all start with &#8220;Why&#8230;&#8221;<br />
Why doesn&#8217;t everyone see You?<br />
Why can&#8217;t my hands be bigger?<br />
Why did love and lonliness both have her face?<br />
Why did the phone have to ring that day?<br />
The world spun through Albuquerque, New Mexico<br />
To a house big enough for our silence.<br />
Again, a ringing phone.<br />
I got the call that explained, at the end, my grandmother said she could see Jesus<br />
Or maybe it was her favorite grandchild whose voice she&#8217;d never hear again<br />
My wife came home and stood at the opposite end of the room<br />
a thousand miles away<br />
Torn between the bitter chill of our dying marriage<br />
And my warm sobbing for my grandmother who was dead<br />
She compromised with a hand on my shoulder<br />
And the world spun faster<br />
It spins through the girl ahead of me in the checkout line who is the love of my life, but neither of us will ever know it.<br />
It spins through the man who sleeps in the alley so I can waste money on a hamburger I didn&#8217;t really want.<br />
It spins through that call I should have made weeks ago to a phone that will never ring again.<br />
It spins through my arrogance and my self-righteousness and my small, small hands.<br />
I&#8217;m sorry I could not catch you.<br />
My friends and I used to say &#8220;Good-bye&#8221;<br />
Now it&#8217;s just &#8220;Don&#8217;t die.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2001/12/02/small-hands/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Victimless Crimes</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2001/11/23/victimless-crimes/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2001/11/23/victimless-crimes/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2001 05:43:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[poetry]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/2001/11/23/victimless-crimes/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Yes, officer, I am now aware that I was 10 miles over the posted speed limit. It&#8217;s just plain cruel to hang such a staggering sunset on yon horizon And not expect a man&#8217;s heart to race toward it, vehicle in tow. Now I suppose you&#8217;re fixing to run my license and have a peek [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Yes, officer, I am now aware that I was 10 miles over the posted speed limit.<br />
It&#8217;s just plain cruel to hang such a staggering sunset on yon horizon<br />
And not expect a man&#8217;s heart to race toward it, vehicle in tow.<br />
Now I suppose you&#8217;re fixing to run my license and have a peek at my record.<br />
Allow me a disclaimer, a few soft words of explanation<br />
That will get our relationship off to a pleasant start.<br />
The parking tickets &#8211; well, I can&#8217;t deny those.<br />
Though, I know you&#8217;ll raise an eyebrow at the library fine.<br />
Yes, it is true: I did check out the entire collection of Sumerian mythology,<br />
Some 57 odd books, from Taylor Memorial, and yes, I never returned them.<br />
Three weeks is hardly adequate time to contemplate the Nam-Shub of Enkidu,<br />
Wouldn&#8217;t you agree?<br />
And I&#8217;m sure the death mark placed on me by the Turkish Government is on file.<br />
You can&#8217;t take a piss in that country without committing some blasphemy or another.<br />
Tucamcari?<br />
Let me ask you something:<br />
Were you even aware of such a smudge on the map before consulting my record?<br />
No, I didn&#8217;t think so.<br />
I&#8217;m sure no one misses it &#8211; I sure don&#8217;t.<br />
Let them build an outlet mall or something there.<br />
Plenty of space for it now.<br />
&#8220;Who is Charlene Friday?&#8221;<br />
Well, once upon a time, I would have said she was my wife.<br />
Nowadays, that&#8217;s just a word in the dictionary between &#8220;Friendship&#8221; and &#8220;Friction.&#8221;<br />
I can see where you&#8217;re going with this, officer.<br />
You could stand there playing priest to my confessor until the shadows tuck in the mountains and kiss them goodnight,<br />
But let me save you the trouble:<br />
I am a guilty man.<br />
But not for anything on your little computer screen.<br />
If you have a moment, I can let you peruse the Right and True account of my life,<br />
Careful and leather-bound,<br />
Right here in the glove compartment.<br />
Fear not!<br />
I am unarmed,<br />
Save for my wicked, wicked tongue.<br />
Here:<br />
I rescued a princess from a faraway tower, but put her in another tower closer to me.<br />
I had a basket of apples, but picked another from my neighbor&#8217;s tree.<br />
I discovered a clear mountain stream and kept it a secret.<br />
I let an entire summer slide past my window without so much as a glance at it.<br />
I had a dream about a net of stars and did not write a poem about it.<br />
Holy music swelled in my chest, yet I did not sing.<br />
I pushed a child.<br />
I laughed at a friend.<br />
But these are all essentially victimless crimes,<br />
Pedestrian cruelties available to common souls,<br />
Loose change in the coat pockets of a more hideous transgression.<br />
All victimless crimes.<br />
I am a villain, true, but officer, please show me the innocent.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2001/11/23/victimless-crimes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
