<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Spring Break 1995 &#8211; First Time Flowing</title>
	<atom:link href="http://www.andremonserrat.com/tag/spring-break-1995/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com</link>
	<description>Scattered pages from an apocryphal diary</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 00:04:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.9</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Spring Break 1995</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/03/31/spring-break-1995/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/03/31/spring-break-1995/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 21:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DePauw]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spring Break 1995]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=650</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I dug up something from the archives and incorporated it into the retroblog. Since it is around spring break now, I thought it appropriate. Spring Break 1995]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I dug up something from the archives and incorporated it into the retroblog. Since it is around spring break now, I thought it appropriate.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.andremonserrat.com/tag/spring-break-1995/">Spring Break 1995</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/03/31/spring-break-1995/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spring Break Day 8</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1995/03/31/spring-break-day-8/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1995/03/31/spring-break-day-8/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 1995 21:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DePauw]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spring Break 1995]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=649</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[As I passed into Tennessee, I was tempted to make a detour into Memphis, but after seeing Steve Timm&#8217;s documentary on Graceland, I decided to steer clear of that realm inhabited by the mad followers of a dead king. As I crossed into Arkansas, I was greeted by a sign reading &#8220;Welcome to Arkansas &#8212; [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As I passed into Tennessee, I was tempted to make a detour into Memphis, but<br />
after seeing Steve Timm&#8217;s documentary on Graceland, I decided to steer clear<br />
of that realm inhabited by the mad followers of a dead king.</p>
<p>As I crossed into Arkansas, I was greeted by a sign reading &#8220;Welcome to<br />
Arkansas &#8212; Home of President Bill Clinton.&#8221;  As though they could legitimate<br />
anything that went on there by the fact that their boy was in the White House.<br />
Arkansas didn&#8217;t have much to say to me or maybe I was too tired to listen.<span id="more-649"></span></p>
<p>On to Missouri.  Once again, I was almost out of gas.  I pulled off the<br />
interstate when I saw a sign that advertised gas.  Up until this point, all such<br />
signs have always meant that I would find about three gas station/food plazas<br />
that were open 24 hours.  Not so here.  There was just an abandoned 76 station<br />
at the edge of the exit ramp.  I decided to venture into the nearby village.</p>
<p>The place had a strip on which every single gas station was closed.<br />
There are various times in my life when I sense that my demise is at least<br />
60% probable in the immediate future.  A little voice inside my head automatically say,<br />
&#8220;Ah, so this is how it ends: impending doom.&#8221;  </p>
<p>This particular situation elicited the response &#8220;Ah, so this is how it ends:<br />
Lost in the middle of nowhere in Missouri at the mercy of<br />
whatever wild animals that might live out here.&#8221;</p>
<p>As I puttered around the next bend in the road, I saw ahead of me a glowing<br />
not unlike the way the gates of heaven must glow.  It was the light of a gas<br />
station.  It was open.  Relieved, I filled my tank and went inside to pay with<br />
my credit card.  I immediately realized that I was Somewhere Else when the<br />
cashier spoke to me in Native Missourian, a language I had never heard.  Through<br />
hand and eyebrow gestures, I was able to convey my intentions to pay for the<br />
gas with a credit card.</p>
<p>As she was swiping the card through the reader, I noticed a point-of-purchase<br />
display on the counter.  It was a collection of audio tapes entitled &#8220;How to<br />
Tell if You&#8217;re a Redneck.&#8221;  It was some comic&#8217;s routine that went like &#8220;If you<br />
think visiting the dentist is something that only happens on TV, well, you might<br />
be a redneck.&#8221;</p>
<p>The cashier informs me that my card is not being accepted by their machine.<br />
I tell her evenly that I&#8217;ve been using it all day and it should work fine.  She<br />
trys it several more times to no avail.  It may as well have been my library<br />
card she was sliding through the machine.  She asked me if I had any cash and I<br />
said no.  As I stood there, I could feel the gaze of her daughter sizing me up<br />
like a new kind of hamburger she wanted to try.</p>
<p>&#8220;Ah, so this is how it ends,&#8221; my mind said dryly, &#8220;kidnapped and raped by<br />
rednecks in the middle of Nowhere, Missouri.&#8221;</p>
<p>The cashier continued to fiddle with the mind-numbingly simple card reader<br />
while I escaped to the restroom.  The handle on the toilet must have been<br />
connected somehow to the reader for when I came back out, the card read just<br />
fine.  I took my card and got the hell out of there.</p>
<p>I had allotted myself three hours out of the twenty four to sleep.  Otherwise<br />
I would have to drive non-stop to get back in time for the job fair.  I slept<br />
a bit at some roadside restaurant and then continued on.</p>
<p>It was early morning in Illinois when I had Cop Encounter #4, the last one<br />
of my journey.</p>
<p>I was cruising along, doing the speed limit (as I had been doing for at least<br />
an hour) when I saw a cop car situated on the grassy median strip between the<br />
highways.  I had this psychic intuition that he was going to pull me over.</p>
<p>As I passed by, sure enough, he pulled into the flow of traffic.  I thought,<br />
&#8220;Okay, okay, I&#8217;m just going to play it real inconspicuous.&#8221;  I slid into the<br />
right lane between two semis and then out again the pass one of them.<br />
That&#8217;s when the guy pulled me over.</p>
<p>He explained to me that he had scene me move in and out between the two trucks<br />
and hadn&#8217;t used my turn signal either time.  This of course explains why he<br />
started to follow me BEFORE I changed lanes, right?</p>
<p>I had to sit with him in his car on the passenger side as he wrote up a<br />
warning for me.  This wasn&#8217;t just a reason to check my record for any drug<br />
related charges, right?  As I sat there he told me how he had thought of<br />
attending DePauw, but had gone somewhere else instead.  He finished the warning<br />
and had me sign it.  He told me to be careful and use those turn signals.</p>
<p>By the time I reached Indiana, I realized that I was going to be at least 2<br />
hours late for the job fair and in no coherent condition anyways.  I decided to<br />
screw the job fair and just go back to Greencastle.  I drove into town, never<br />
so glad to see it as I was at that moment, and took the car to the car wash.</p>
<p>Even after a furious robotic scrubdown, the roof of my car still had the<br />
writing &#8220;Bad Fucking Car&#8221; on it from when Ryan, Josh, Rod and everyone went to<br />
see &#8220;Pulp Fiction&#8221; last semester.</p>
<p>Then I took it to get an oil change.  I explained to them that yes, I had just<br />
been in about a week ago and yes, I had since driven almost 4000 miles since<br />
then.</p>
<p>The dorms didn&#8217;t open until Sunday at noon, so I needed a place to stay.  I<br />
considered staying at Freedom, but I wasn&#8217;t sure any of the guys were back.  I<br />
thought of Greg Stephan&#8217;s place and would have tried there had I not stopped<br />
at Tom Chiarella&#8217;s first.  He graciously allowed me to stay in the guest room<br />
until Sunday as long as I was gone during the day so the kids wouldn&#8217;t be<br />
freaked out.</p>
<p>I slept for a while, hung out, did some other things.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1995/03/31/spring-break-day-8/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spring Break Day 7</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1995/03/30/spring-break-day-7/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1995/03/30/spring-break-day-7/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 1995 21:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DePauw]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spring Break 1995]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=648</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[After sleeping in the parking lots of Wal-Mart and Denny&#8217;s, I headed to Galveston, an island city of hotels. I drove along the coast of the Gulf of Mexico. It was about 4 or 5 in the morning. I parked at a Kroger&#8217;s so I could walk down to the beach. I stood there for [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After sleeping in the parking lots of Wal-Mart and Denny&#8217;s, I headed to<br />
Galveston, an island city of hotels.  I drove along the coast of the Gulf of<br />
Mexico.  It was about 4 or 5 in the morning.  I parked at a Kroger&#8217;s so I could<br />
walk down to the beach.  I stood there for a long time, out at the ocean,<br />
mesmerized by the sound of waves slipping in and out.</p>
<p>I returned to the car to rest some more.  The dawn came, cold and lifeless.<br />
I had hoped it would be clear so that I could see the sun rise, but I was<br />
denied.<span id="more-648"></span></p>
<p>Getting out again, I had some bread.  As I tore off a chunk, a large seagull<br />
landed near by.  It regarded my bread hungrily.  I tossed it a piece which it<br />
swallowed with no grace at all.  A few more gulls landed.  I tossed a few<br />
pieces of bread among them and they devoured the bread.  I realized that seagull<br />
s were ugly, vicious birds.  Suddenly I was surrounded by about twenty of<br />
them.  In numbers they know no fear.  They hovered around me, forming a<br />
flying dome of hungry birds.  It was truly frightening.   I jumped in my car<br />
before I could get whitewashed, pecked or carried away.</p>
<p>After a while the birds left.</p>
<p>It was around this time that I thought about returning to Indiana.  I was<br />
supposed to go to this job fair in Indy Friday afternoon.  I then realized that<br />
I had grossly underestimated how long it would take me to return.  I needed to<br />
leave Texas as soon as possible.</p>
<p>But my mission was not yet complete.  I wanted to wade out into the ocean.<br />
I put on some shorts and headed back to the beach.  Most other people were<br />
wearing jackets since it was cold.  But I had slept through a Minnesota<br />
winter night unscathed and such things no longer bothered me.</p>
<p>On the beach I took off my shoes and socks and waded out into the surf<br />
with my camera.  I took some pictures and collected some sand and water in<br />
a bottle to take back to Alex.</p>
<p>Hopping back in my car, probably laughing, I headed out of Texas and towards<br />
Louisiana.  Louisiana is a lot like Dagobah, except its sunier and there are<br />
paved roads.  Otherwise, its just a lot of swamps full of scaly creeping<br />
things.</p>
<p>It was in this state that I had Cop Encounter #3.</p>
<p>The cop pulls me off the road and gestures that I get out of the car and<br />
stand between my car and his.  This cop was short, but built like a wall of<br />
bricks.  Tanned and serious.  Of course he had to know where I was going and<br />
where I had come from.  He couldn&#8217;t believe that I had wanted to visit Texas<br />
for spring break.</p>
<p>He explained that I had been going 71 in a 65 mph zone.  And then he asked<br />
me, get this, &#8220;What&#8217;s yer big hurry?&#8221;  I&#8217;m going six miles over the limit and<br />
I&#8217;m in a hurry?  They must take things pretty slow here in Louisiana.  I told<br />
him that I just wasn&#8217;t paying attention.  He wanted to see my vehicle registration.<br />
As I opened the passenger door and reached for the glove compartment,<br />
he stopped me and asked if I had any guns in there.</p>
<p>Weapons?  Me?!  I told him &#8220;no.&#8221;</p>
<p>After he looked at the registration, he had me stand away from the car as<br />
he returned to his own vehicle.  He opened the rear passenger door and brought<br />
out a leash.  Next thing I know he&#8217;s bringing out this dog to take a pee in<br />
the grass.  I didn&#8217;t recognize the breed and figured it was vat grown,<br />
genetically engineered to perform the duties of a police dog.  He trotted the<br />
dog over to my car and walked it around twice, letting the thing get a good<br />
sniff.  Drugs, of course.  The dog seemed satisfied that I was not harboring<br />
bricks of hash and nodded up to the cop.</p>
<p>They let me go with a warning.</p>
<p>I had been stopped three times now in three different states.  I was feeling<br />
pretty notorious and invincible.</p>
<p>As I continued to drive through the swamp state, I was constantly tempted<br />
to stop at a crocodile farm or Cajun restaurant, but i was short on time.</p>
<p>Soon (well, relatively soon) I was in Mississippi.  While passing along<br />
a stretch of green forest, I noticed a dead armadillo lying by the side of the<br />
road.  One of my only regrets is that I didn&#8217;t stop and bring it with me so<br />
I could walk into Jeff&#8217;s room and say, &#8220;Hey, look what I found!&#8221;</p>
<p>As I approached the state border, night began to fall.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1995/03/30/spring-break-day-7/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spring Break Day 6</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1995/03/29/spring-break-day-6/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1995/03/29/spring-break-day-6/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 1995 21:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DePauw]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spring Break 1995]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=647</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I woke up to find myself at a rest stop in Kansas. I took an ad hoc shower in the restroom using only a sink and a cup. I got back on the road and headed into Oklahoma. I kept thinking of how my friend Brandon would yell &#8220;Oklahoma! Oklahoma!&#8221; like Steve Martin in the [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I woke up to find myself at a rest stop in Kansas.  I took an ad hoc<br />
shower in the restroom using only a sink and a cup.</p>
<p>I got back on the road and headed into Oklahoma.  I kept thinking of how<br />
my friend Brandon would yell &#8220;Oklahoma! Oklahoma!&#8221; like Steve Martin in the<br />
movie &#8220;Dirty Rotten Scoundrels.&#8221;  I stopped at the Oklahoma Trading Post,<br />
looking for any cool cowboy gear.  I was looking for one of those neat poncho<br />
things that Alex has.  They didn&#8217;t have any.<span id="more-647"></span></p>
<p>I can&#8217;t remember anything interesting about Oklahoma, so I&#8217;ll just jump ahead<br />
to Texas.  Texas is a beautiful state and I think I liked it the most out of<br />
all the others I had seen.  It is huge and full of variety: forests, seashore<br />
and desert.  I wish I could have seen the desert, but there was no time.</p>
<p>As I approached Dallas, my mind played the theme to the TV show.  I wanted<br />
to stop in the city, but the traffic was so insane and frightening that I<br />
decided to just keep on going towards Houston.</p>
<p>Two hours north of Houston I stopped to call Jeff and Alex.  I was feeling<br />
lonely and wanted to hear a familiar voice.  I also wanted to hear Alex<br />
freaking out when I told him where I was.  I was not disappointed and it<br />
made the whole trip worthwhile just to hear him go off.  Jeff just said,<br />
&#8220;What the fuck, dude?&#8221;  Alex asked me to get him some water from the ocean.</p>
<p>I hung up and was heading back to my car which was parked beside the<br />
convenience store.  I noticed something on the ground.  While on the phone<br />
I had noticed something before and my mind had for some reason decided they<br />
were rabbit droppings.  Why I thought that was perfectly reasonable, I don&#8217;t<br />
know.  Upon closer inspection I saw that what I was looking at was<br />
several hundred dead roaches lying on the sidewalk.  I got into my car and fled.</p>
<p>By the time I made it to Houston, it was late and I was very tired.  I<br />
pulled into a Wal-Mart parking lot and slept for a while.  When I got up<br />
I drove some more to Denny&#8217;s and had a late night/early morning breakfast.<br />
Then I slept in the parking lot some more.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1995/03/29/spring-break-day-6/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title></title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1995/03/28/646/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1995/03/28/646/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 1995 21:09:23 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DePauw]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spring Break 1995]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=646</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I woke up at 5 AM. The inside of my car&#8217;s windows were covered with ice. I was so cold. My joints ached and everything felt sore. Moving was an effort. I crawled into the front seat and managed to get my boots on and start the car to get some warmth going. I felt [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I woke up at 5 AM.  The inside of my car&#8217;s windows were covered with ice.</p>
<p>I was so cold.  My joints ached and everything felt sore.  Moving was an<br />
effort.  I crawled into the front seat and managed to get my boots on and<br />
start the car to get some warmth going.  I felt like the conquering hero;<br />
a survivor.<span id="more-646"></span></p>
<p>After I was reasonably warm, I drove to the gas station and got gas.  There<br />
were these two townfolk in there.  One of them looks me over and says &#8220;Who<br />
are you supposed to be, Wyatt Erp?&#8221;  &#8220;This is just how I dress,&#8221; was all I<br />
had to say.  I asked them if there was anyplace open this early for breakfast<br />
and they recommended the Milkbar.</p>
<p>I walk into this place which was the Greencastle equivalent of Nina&#8217;s Java<br />
Junction.  I mean the Ely equivalent.  Anyways, there&#8217;s all these old guys<br />
sitting at the counter and the waitress greets everyone by name and has a<br />
cup of coffee ready for them.  I sit right in the middle and order an english<br />
muffin and coffee.  No one speaks to me.</p>
<p>I kill some time.  Drive around.  Go to Hardees for another breakfast.  I<br />
stay there about two hours, reading.  Then I head for the Wolf Center which<br />
is about to open.  The place was up on a hill, a lodge-like structure you<br />
might see in a national park.  In front of the place were statues of wolves<br />
running.</p>
<p>I waited for them to open the doors and entered in with a group of people.</p>
<p>I paid the admission and went into the museum area of the place.  Here one<br />
could learn all about wolves: what they ate, how they hunted, pack patterns,<br />
the behaviors of different wolves in the hierarchy, how to distinguish an<br />
Alpha wolf from the others, etc.  There were all sorts of interactive video<br />
and audio kiosks.  In the center of the area was a large diorama of stuffed<br />
wolves.  Two were playing and two were killing a deer while the others were<br />
just chilling.</p>
<p>There were a bunch of children running around the place, which annoyed<br />
me.  One of the boys kept asking me &#8220;Who are YOU?&#8221;  I heard him tell his<br />
mother that I was the wolf man.  I smiled inwardly at that.</p>
<p>After I had checked the museum out I walked to the back of the center<br />
where the classrooms were.  There was an area of seats facing a large picture<br />
window.  On the other side of the window was a large fenced off area.<br />
Basking in the sun, about fifty feet away, were two wolves.</p>
<p>Wolves.  Right there.  They were beautiful.  Occasionally one would get<br />
up and stretch or look around before lying back down.  They were lean and<br />
graceful.  I just stood and watched them sleeping.  Sometimes wolves sleep<br />
twenty hours a day, if they&#8217;ve had enough to eat.</p>
<p>Later on, this woman came out to talk about the wolves.  She passed around<br />
bones and wolf pelts for the audience to examine.  Then she went outside and<br />
coaxed all the wolves down with these deer biscuits or something.  They have<br />
four wolves (one male, three female) in captivity there.  Each had distinctive<br />
markings and personality.</p>
<p>Sometimes they would come really close to the window and would stand within<br />
an arm&#8217;s reach.  It made me happy to watch them walk around and eat the food<br />
and stare at the audience.</p>
<p>I left feeling that I had accomplished my mission.  I had had the idea<br />
that maybe I would be allowed to play with the wolves since I was on a holy<br />
quest, but no.  I wrote to Ryan about the experience and mailed him his<br />
letter.</p>
<p>Now what?  After seeing the wolves, the only plans I had were to go places<br />
I had never been.  Originally, I was thinking about seeing Montana, but it<br />
was just too cold up there.  I thought of Beth and Sheila and all those<br />
other people getting tans.  I wanted to go someplace warm and sunny.<br />
Hey, I&#8217;ve never been to Texas, I thought.</p>
<p>That&#8217;s what I would do:  I&#8217;d drive south to the ocean and walk out into<br />
the Gulf of Mexico!  That became the new goal.  I thought of the play I had<br />
just been in and thought how cool it would be to find some shady bar in<br />
Texas and play pool with a one-armed man.</p>
<p>I headed south, back through Minnesota and down into Iowa.  As soon as I<br />
crossed the border into Iowa, the sky turned dark and oppressive, as though<br />
the state knew I had been writing stories about it.  It was here that I had<br />
police encounter #2.</p>
<p>It was late at night and I had just finished listening to my audio CD of<br />
Gibson&#8217;s &#8220;Neuromancer.&#8221;  I was excited and not paying attention to the<br />
speedometer.  I got pulled over.  The guy was young and nice.  I was going<br />
10 MPH over the limit.</p>
<p>&#8220;Tell you what,&#8221; he says.  &#8220;I&#8217;m going to save you some money and let<br />
you go with a warning.&#8221;  I thanked the guy and continued on.  I had told<br />
him I was going to Texas and he asked me if I thought I could make it that<br />
night.  I had no idea how far away it was.</p>
<p>Missouri.  Kansas.  Driving across a state seemed like nothing at all to<br />
me.  Every time I crossed a new state line, I laughed like a madman.  I could<br />
do anything I wanted.  It&#8217;s good to take a road trip alone;  all you have<br />
are your own thoughts.  I had incredible mental conversations.</p>
<p>I was getting tired, so I pulled into a rest stop and slept there until<br />
morning.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1995/03/28/646/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spring Break Day 4</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1995/03/27/spring-break-day-4/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1995/03/27/spring-break-day-4/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 1995 21:06:18 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DePauw]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spring Break 1995]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=645</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I woke up and took the only shower I would get all week. I had a decision to make: The weather forecast called for a severe snowstorm that would sweep across the entire state. I had called the Wolf Center and they didn&#8217;t open until Tuesday. If I stayed even a few hours, the storm [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I woke up and took the only shower I would get all week.  I had a decision<br />
to make:  The weather forecast called for a severe snowstorm that would sweep<br />
across the entire state.  I had called the Wolf Center and they didn&#8217;t open<br />
until Tuesday.  If I stayed even a few hours, the storm would hit.  If I went<br />
to Ely, I would have to wait until the next day for the center to open.</p>
<p>I decided to go it.<span id="more-645"></span></p>
<p>I headed north, driving along Lake Superior.  It was a huge patch of cold<br />
blue which turned into white ice near the shore.  At one point I saw several<br />
big ships, tankers, that were frozen on the ice.</p>
<p>The road then wound through Superior National Forest which was just beautiful.<br />
I had never been in a forest that big.  I saw perhaps three other vehicles<br />
on my journey through the forest.  The road was winding and treacherous with<br />
snow.  I expected a storm to hit me at any moment and then I would be screwed.<br />
I stopped along the way by this abandoned log cabin to make a sandwich &#8212;<br />
that was my staple food: peanut butter sandwiches.  They taste different<br />
when you make them yourself out in the middle of the wilderness.  Before I<br />
started along again, I took a Twin Peaks-like picture of the road.  You gotta<br />
see it.</p>
<p>Ely was two hours north of Duluth, within 100 miles of the Canadian border.<br />
It turns out that the weathermen were completely mistaken.  No storm.  Not<br />
even any snow.  They joked about it on the radio for the next day.</p>
<p>Ely is a lot like Greencastle in that it is very small and in the middle of<br />
nowhere.  It is also a lot like Twin Peaks because of the trees, the atmosphere,<br />
the logging business and because I found a dead body washed up on shore there.<br />
Just kidding!  It did remind me a lot of Twin Peaks, though.  The main strip of<br />
the town was all about canoe, camping and wilderness outfitters.  These places<br />
were punctuated by saloons and gift shops.</p>
<p>I wandered about for a while, looking in the shops and such.  There wasn&#8217;t<br />
much to see and I realized that this place could easily bore me out of my<br />
mind.  I had a whole day which I pretty much had to spend there, though.<br />
I drove to a larger neighboring city, Virginia, which was pretty much like<br />
driving to Bloomington, but it wasn&#8217;t as fun when I got there.</p>
<p>So I went back to Ely and hung out in the library where I read for a few<br />
hours.  As it got later, I decided to go to a bar and check out the night life.<br />
I entered &#8220;Dee&#8217;s Bar and Lounge&#8221; to find the place deserted except for an old wo<br />
man and two guys talking to the bartender.  I bought a rum and coke, a pack<br />
of Marlboros and sat down in a booth.</p>
<p>The Rockford Files was on the television and I pretended to watch.  But I<br />
was really listening to the stories these guys were telling.  Most of them<br />
had to do with young girls, how long it take to drive to Minneapolis, and the<br />
police using inflatable sex dolls to entrap speeders.  I&#8217;ll go into more<br />
detail for those of you who really want to know.</p>
<p>I stayed there until I felt uncomfortable and then returned to my car.</p>
<p>I went back to the library and read until it closed.  Hoo rah.<br />
It was late, so I decided to look for a place to sleep.  I cruised the<br />
back streets of the town, looking for someplace out of the way.  At each<br />
likely spot, my mind played a worst case scenario about what would happen if<br />
someone found me.  These thoughts ranged from some psycho breaking in to the<br />
car to a little old woman thinking I was the casualty of a drug deal gone<br />
bad, so she calls the cops.</p>
<p>I finally found a hospital parking lot with cars in it all the time.  I<br />
took a spot in the back row, climbed into the back seat and curled up<br />
under my blankets.</p>
<p>I forgot that it was still winter there.  More in the morning&#8230;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1995/03/27/spring-break-day-4/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spring Break Day 3</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1995/03/26/spring-break-day-3/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1995/03/26/spring-break-day-3/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 1995 21:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DePauw]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spring Break 1995]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=644</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I woke up early in the morning, having forgotten where I was. Huddled in the back seat of my car, I peeked out through the windows at a cold grey dawn.  I was in the parking lot of the Mall of America.  There were some security people around, but otherwise I didn&#8217;t see anyone.  It [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I woke up early in the morning, having forgotten where I was.<br />
Huddled in the back seat of my car, I peeked out through the<br />
windows at a cold grey dawn.  I was in the parking lot of the<br />
Mall of America.  There were some security people around, but<br />
otherwise I didn&#8217;t see anyone.  It was about 6 or 7 AM.  I slept<br />
some more. Then I got up and had a bowl of cereal.  I finished<br />
reading &#8220;Service for the Dead,&#8221; a Vietnam novel and worked on my<br />
letter to Ryan.  It was late and wouldn&#8217;t arrive in time for his<br />
birthday.</p>
<p>Around 8 I went into the mall and watched the mall-walkers do<br />
their rounds.  Since it was Sunday, the stores didn&#8217;t open until<br />
11.  I explored the first floor just to get my bearings and<br />
figure out how the place was laid out.<span id="more-644"></span></p>
<p>The Mall of America is probably one of the neatest places I&#8217;ve<br />
ever visited.  It is four stories tall and divided into four<br />
wings at each compass point.  Your average mall (like Greenwood<br />
or Castleton) would probably take up two of this mall&#8217;s wings.<br />
The place was just gigantic.  There was an amusement park in the<br />
center complete with roller coaster and log ride.  At each wing<br />
there was something different.  One wing had Lego Land.  It was<br />
the size of a small house.  Everything was built from giant<br />
Legos.  There were dinosaurs, guys on motorcycles, a space ship,<br />
etc.  The little Lego people were about as tall as I am.</p>
<p>Besides having every store I had ever known, they had many<br />
specialty shops.  One really cool place was the Rainforest Cafe.<br />
The place looked like it had been chiseled out of rock.  There<br />
were tropical plants everywhere.  There was a heavy steam<br />
billowing through the place and every once in a while there was a<br />
thunder storm.  Live parrots greeted you when you walked into the<br />
gift shop area.  Just outrageous.</p>
<p>On one floor there was a laser tag arena.  There was a comic<br />
book store with t-shirts of the Tick!  Amazingly enough, I didn&#8217;t<br />
buy one.  They had a Starlog store, completely devoted to all<br />
sorts of science fiction: Star Wars, Star Trek, Battlestar<br />
Galactica, Dr. Who, X-Men, Robotech, etc.  Hey Rod, they were<br />
selling Breetai and Khyron action figures for $20 each!  The<br />
whole back room was devoted to Star Trek.</p>
<p>Chris and Rod, you would have loved the Astronomy/World of<br />
Science and Science Fiction store they had.  In one corner there<br />
were telescopes and star charts, in another there were Star Trek<br />
figures and robot models.</p>
<p>There were many clothing stores there, Beth.  I wished you<br />
were there so we could have gone shopping again.<br />
On the top floor there was a Hooters, Planet Hollywood,<br />
American Sportsbar and a 13 theater General Cinemas.  The<br />
Sportsbar had virtual reality games.  I saw that they were<br />
showing &#8220;Just Cause&#8221; in the theater and decided to see it later<br />
that afternoon.</p>
<p>Before the mall opened, I sat on a bench and read &#8220;The Left<br />
Hand of Darkness.&#8221;  It was very relaxing.  When the stores<br />
finally opened, more people had shown up.  I had had this idea<br />
that I would have the entire mall to myself.  Suddenly the quiet<br />
mall was filled with the familiar bustle of mall rats.  Oh well.</p>
<p>I stopped in the Natural Wonders store to ask about wolves.<br />
The lady there told me that the place to go was Ely (EE-LEE).<br />
That&#8217;s where the International Wolf Center was.  I asked her how<br />
far away it was and she said it was about 6 hours north.<br />
6 hours.  Into the snow.  I&#8217;d be right near Canada for crying<br />
out loud.  But the wolves&#8230;  That was the goal of my mission: to<br />
see the wolves.  How much would I risk to see them?  I had to<br />
think about that.  In the meantime, I continued to explore the<br />
mall.</p>
<p>I spent most of the day there.  So many people.  Most of them<br />
had that Minnesota accent.  It&#8217;s so endearing, don&#8217;t ya know?<br />
I&#8217;ll have to imitate it for you some time.  Going to the mall<br />
usually drains something out of me.  It&#8217;s as though it requires<br />
emotional energy to take in everyone around me, comprehending the<br />
scope of humanity.  But not there.  I was happy.  I could look<br />
out over a balcony on the fourth floor and see a forest inside a<br />
mall.  There was a gigantic snoopy sitting beside a swimming<br />
pool-sized water dish.  I just smiled and smiled.</p>
<p>In the afternoon I saw &#8220;Just Cause.&#8221;  It has Sean Connery,<br />
Lawrence Fishbourn and Ed Harris.  It&#8217;s a murder mystery movie<br />
which I highly recommend.</p>
<p>After the movie I decided it was time to go.  I had made my<br />
decision: I was going to see the wolves.  I checked the map and<br />
decided that I would drive as far as I could that night and then<br />
check into a motel since it would be too cold to sleep in my car.<br />
While I was sitting there in the parking lot, a car rolled<br />
across the way from another parking space and bumped into the car<br />
next to me, blocking my exit.  It had narrowly missed me.<br />
Apparently the guy had forgotten to put his parking break on and<br />
the lot had a slight slope.  I went inside and called security<br />
and the mall secretary announced that the owner of the car should<br />
report to the parking lot.  The guy and a rent-a-cop showed up<br />
and worked things out, allowing me to leave.</p>
<p>I drove until late, stopping in Duluth.  I found a place<br />
called the Spirit Mountain Lodge and got a room there.  It was<br />
comfy and warm.  I watched the end of &#8220;Backdraft&#8221; on TV and then<br />
went to sleep.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1995/03/26/spring-break-day-3/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spring Break Day 2</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1995/03/25/spring-break-day-2/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1995/03/25/spring-break-day-2/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 1995 20:53:56 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DePauw]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spring Break 1995]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=643</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I woke up in Josh&#8217;s apartment, had some cereal, and watched &#8220;The Tick&#8221; and &#8220;Spiderman.&#8221;  They were both reruns.  It was the Tick Vs. Mr. Mental, the first one I had seen. I wanted to take a shower, but apparently the hot water heater had exploded in the night, so there was nothing but ice [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I woke up in Josh&#8217;s apartment, had some cereal, and watched<br />
&#8220;The Tick&#8221; and &#8220;Spiderman.&#8221;  They were both reruns.  It was the<br />
Tick Vs. Mr. Mental, the first one I had seen.</p>
<p>I wanted to take a shower, but apparently the hot water heater<br />
had exploded in the night, so there was nothing but ice water.  I<br />
looked upon this as a good thing, as I would have to get used to<br />
not taking showers for the rest of the week.</p>
<p>I called up Jeff to see if we were going to get together and<br />
do something.  I told him I wanted to check out a few stores<br />
before I headed back to Kennelworth where he lived.  Josh and I<br />
headed out to the city on a marvelous sunny day.<span id="more-643"></span></p>
<p>F.A.O. Schwartz was our first stop.  It was a giant department<br />
store-sized toy store.  The place was a candy-coated Willy Wonka<br />
Disney cartoon theme park ride come to life.  I was frightened.<br />
Giant teddy bears and smiling clocks loomed everywhere.  And<br />
toys.  Toys all around me.  I played with a few things before I<br />
started to feel claustrophobic.  Then we left.</p>
<p>A new Borders Books and Music had opened up on a corner.  Four<br />
stories of books, magazines, CDs and computer software.  I<br />
browsed through every floor and didn&#8217;t buy a single thing.  The<br />
part of my conscience that presides over consumer goods has<br />
Ryan&#8217;s voice.  &#8220;You don&#8217;t need that,&#8221; it kept saying.  &#8220;When will<br />
you have time to read that?&#8221; or &#8220;You already have one of those.&#8221;</p>
<p>After returning to Josh&#8217;s, I finished most of my pizza and<br />
bade him farewell, after shelling out $17.00 for overnight<br />
parking.  In some cities, that would buy me a motel room.  I just<br />
paid $17.00 so my car could have a good night&#8217;s rest.  It turned<br />
out that that would be the last rest it would have in some time.</p>
<p>Jeff and Alex weren&#8217;t home when I got to his house.  I sat in<br />
his living room, reading, until they returned.  Then we all went<br />
out to Best Buy after stopping at the tobacconist so Jeff could<br />
buy some cloves.  I had never been to Best Buy before.  Their<br />
prices were ridiculously low.  We waited forever for Alex to<br />
figure out what CDs he wanted to buy.</p>
<p>We returned to Jeff&#8217;s and when it became apparent that nothing<br />
interesting was going to happen in the immediate future, I<br />
decided it was time to move on.  My plan was to go to Minnesota<br />
and find wolves.  I hugged them goodbye and took off on route 94<br />
west.</p>
<p>This is where my journey began.</p>
<p>I hit Milwaukee, Wisconsin in the early evening.  As I drove<br />
through I thought, &#8220;Hey, this is where they invented beer!&#8221;<br />
Maybe I would visit a brewery.  But I reconsidered when I<br />
realized that it would be akin to a DePauw fraternity&#8217;s concept<br />
of nirvana.  So I drove on through.</p>
<p>All along the way I had been seeing billboards for the<br />
&#8220;Hochunk Casino.&#8221;  Hmmm, that sounded interesting.  I had never<br />
been in a casino before.  I stood outside one in Atlantic City,<br />
but I wasn&#8217;t old enough at the time to go in.  The casino was in<br />
Minnesota, a few miles off the interstate.</p>
<p>The Hochunk Casino was about the size of a small airport.  I<br />
had to park about a half mile away (or so it seemed).  You might<br />
have thought you were parking at King&#8217;s Island or something.  I<br />
entered through the glass doors into a wash of bright flashing<br />
lights.  The floor was thick with people and tight lanes of slot<br />
machines.</p>
<p>The sensation was like being at an amusement park, trying to<br />
decide what to ride first.  There were different styles of slot<br />
machines, but they all operated on the same principle: ya gotta<br />
line up dese three little pictures.  The more you bet, the more<br />
you could win.  Of course.</p>
<p>I had vowed that if I ever went to a casino, the money I spent<br />
there would come from one pocket and the money I won would go in<br />
another and never the two should meet.  I got a bunch of quarters<br />
and sat down in front of one of the devices.  It was mind-<br />
bogglingly simple, reminding me of the computerized versions I<br />
had on my computer.  I almost forgot I was playing for real<br />
money.  I lost most of the time, but got a weird Pavlovian thrill<br />
when the bells and whistles went off.  My mind started to play<br />
games with me.  It claimed to see some kind of pattern forming<br />
and if I just kept playing, mathematical statistics would<br />
overcome luck and force the machine to spit out a mountain of<br />
quarters.  I looked at the person next to me.  Their bin was<br />
brimming with silver.  If this mere housewife could win a pile,<br />
then why couldn&#8217;t I?</p>
<p>Fifteen dollars later I was headed for the exit.  I had bet<br />
everything from both pockets.  The potential for disaster waited<br />
in the wings like some mad harpy.  I escaped while my reason<br />
still had both hands on the oars.</p>
<p>Getting in my car, I left the Hochunk Casino behind and set<br />
out to find a place to sleep.  I had this idea that I could sneak<br />
into one of the nearby campgrounds.  Unfortunately, they were<br />
closed at this time of year.   So I returned to the interstate in<br />
search of some safe spot to stop for the night.</p>
<p>I pulled off again near the towns of Millston and Hixton (I&#8217;m<br />
not joking).  I don&#8217;t know if I was in one or the other.<br />
Whichever it was, the town comprised of a gas station and a few<br />
houses.  I crept slowly along, looking for a spot to stow away<br />
for the night.  I made one turn off the road and fond myself on a<br />
winding unlit path.  Not good, I thought.  Maybe I ought to get<br />
back on the interstate and find some nice, well-lit parking lot.<br />
Before I could act on this sage advice offered up by my self-<br />
preservation system, Discordia, that reality-shredding goddess of<br />
chaos, capered onto the scene and lobbed a bad luck grenade in<br />
the form of a police car, lights flashing red and white.<br />
Hmmm, was all I could think.</p>
<p>What follows is Drey&#8217;s Police Encounter #1.</p>
<p>The officer, a weasel-looking guy with glasses and a mustache<br />
approached my car and shined his flashlight around inside.  I had<br />
my license ready for him.<br />
&#8220;You seem a bit agitated,&#8221; he said.<br />
&#8220;I&#8217;m, uh, lost&#8230;&#8221;<br />
&#8220;Oh, you&#8217;re LOST, eh?&#8221;<br />
&#8220;Yes.&#8221;<br />
&#8220;Did you see that stop sign back there?&#8221;<br />
&#8220;No.&#8221;  I had no idea what he was talking about.<br />
&#8220;You DIDN&#8217;T see that stop sign back there?&#8221;<br />
&#8220;No, look, I wasn&#8217;t trying to&#8230;&#8221;<br />
&#8220;You didn&#8217;t see me sitting right by the stop sign?&#8221;<br />
&#8220;Ah, no, I didn&#8217;t see the sign; I guess I wasn&#8217;t paying<br />
attention&#8230;&#8221;<br />
&#8220;You smoke pot?&#8221;<br />
&#8220;No,&#8221; I said.<br />
&#8220;Oh, you DON&#8217;T do you?&#8221;<br />
He shined his light at my crotch where I had placed my CD<br />
player.<br />
&#8220;What&#8217;s that?  A CD player?&#8221; he inquired.<br />
&#8220;Yes.&#8221;<br />
&#8220;What&#8217;s it plugged into?&#8221;<br />
&#8220;What do you mean?&#8221;<br />
&#8220;Well, it&#8217;s a CD player, isn&#8217;t it?  It&#8217;s got to be plugged<br />
into something.&#8221;<br />
&#8220;I, ah, have it wired into the cassette deck&#8230;&#8221;<br />
&#8220;What? Where&#8217;s the headphones?&#8221;<br />
&#8220;I don&#8217;t need headphones with this.&#8221;  I couldn&#8217;t believe this<br />
guy.<br />
&#8220;Oh, something NEW, eh?  Well, why don&#8217;t you open it up for<br />
me?&#8221;<br />
I opened the CD player, revealing a CD.<br />
&#8220;It&#8217;s a CD,&#8221; I observed.<br />
&#8220;Okay,&#8221; he couldn&#8217;t get me there.  &#8220;What&#8217;s in that bag?  Why<br />
don&#8217;t you open that bag and show me what&#8217;s in there.&#8221; He pointed<br />
to my black school backpack.<br />
&#8220;It&#8217;s my bookbag,&#8221; I explained, opening it.  &#8220;Here&#8217;s a book.<br />
And a folder.  Look, here&#8217;s another book.  What do you want to<br />
see?&#8221;  I was getting sarcastic.<br />
&#8220;What are you looking for down here?&#8221;<br />
&#8220;Well, I thought there was a town or something here, but<br />
obviously there isn&#8217;t, so I think I&#8217;ll probably get back on the<br />
express way.&#8221;<br />
&#8220;Uh-huh.  Wait just a minute.&#8221;  He returned to his car to run<br />
what I assumes were routine checks on my license.  He returned<br />
after a few minutes with another odd question.<br />
&#8220;Is that the only jacket you have?  Were you wearing another<br />
jacket before?&#8221;  I was wearing my black trenchcoat like I always<br />
do and had brought no other coat with me.<br />
&#8220;This is the only coat I have.&#8221;<br />
&#8220;Well, we just had some guy hold up a store down here, so<br />
we&#8217;ve been looking for him.&#8221;<br />
Ah, the truth comes out.<br />
&#8220;Well, I didn&#8217;t steal anything&#8230;&#8221;<br />
&#8220;Why don&#8217;t you move some of that stuff around in the back<br />
seat.  Show me what you have back there.&#8221;  He wasn&#8217;t finished.<br />
I moved my pillow to reveal my CD collection.<br />
&#8220;Why look, it&#8217;s my CD collection. What do want to see?!&#8221;<br />
&#8220;All right,&#8221; he seemed satisfied with that.  He gave me<br />
directions back to the interstate and warned me that &#8220;Those stop<br />
signs mean STOP!&#8221;</p>
<p>As I maneuvered back to the highway, I passed the intersection<br />
where I had supposedly run the stop sign.  On the left hand side<br />
of the road was a post about a foot tall.  On the post was a stop<br />
sign no wider than my hand. It was apparently for snowmobiles.<br />
I figured that I couldn&#8217;t stop anywhere within fifty miles of<br />
Hixton since the cops were probably still looking for this guy.<br />
I ended up stopping at a 24-hour restaurant and napping for a<br />
bit.  Then I kept driving.</p>
<p>I decided to visit the Mall of America before seeking out the<br />
wolves.  Jeff&#8217;s mom had told me about it. It is literally the<br />
biggest mall in the country.  She might as well have said, &#8220;Hey,<br />
Drey, I know where there&#8217;s a magic door that leads to Narnia.&#8221;</p>
<p>As I drove, it began to snow.  It was still winter in<br />
Minnesota.  I made it to Bloomington, where the mall was and<br />
parked right in front of it.  To me this was like camping out in<br />
front of the gates to Disney World the night before it opens.  I<br />
crawled into the back seat and fell asleep.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1995/03/25/spring-break-day-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spring Break Day 1</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1995/03/24/spring-break-day-1/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1995/03/24/spring-break-day-1/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 1995 20:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DePauw]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spring Break 1995]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=642</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The day began like most Fridays.  I had no classes, so I had the whole morning to prepare for the journey.  I packed a suitcase full of clothes and toiletries.  I selected a bunch of CDs to keep me sane.  Since I would be sleeping in my car, I took my blankets and pillow.  I [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The day began like most Fridays.  I had no classes, so I had<br />
the whole morning to prepare for the journey.  I packed a<br />
suitcase full of clothes and toiletries.  I selected a bunch of<br />
CDs to keep me sane.  Since I would be sleeping in my car, I took<br />
my blankets and pillow.  I also brought some &#8220;food.&#8221;  That was<br />
all. I filled my escape pod with these things and wondered where<br />
Alex and Jeff were going to put their stuff, let alone their bodies.</p>
<p>I also took the car in for an oil change.  It needed it.  One<br />
of these days the escape pod is going to fall apart into its<br />
component Lego pieces and I&#8217;ll be up shit creek.<br />
I told Alex and Jeff that I wanted to leave at noon.  That<br />
meant they were to have eaten at 11:30.  Of course, as things<br />
with this group go, Alex was just getting up just before noon.<br />
He said it would take only five minutes to pack and shower.</p>
<p>Sure.<span id="more-642"></span></p>
<p>Alex was accounted for, but where was Jeff?  I had knocked on<br />
his door and called his room, but no luck.  Johnny had done the<br />
same. He wasn&#8217;t at the Hub or anywhere he would normally be.</p>
<p>It was 12:30.</p>
<p>I couldn&#8217;t believe he would do this to me.  I left a message<br />
on his board: &#8220;Where the fuck are you?  If I don&#8217;t find you by<br />
1:00, you&#8217;re WALKING!&#8221;  Alex and I tried to think of where he<br />
could be.  Then a thought struck me:  &#8220;Maybe he really is in his<br />
room.  Maybe he&#8217;s just sleeping really really hard.&#8221;  Following<br />
this hunch I went back upstairs and pounded on his door with<br />
renewed vigor.  I was rewarded with a groggy &#8220;Whut?&#8221;<br />
He had been there the whole time.  We got him up and showered<br />
and such.  Then we took off.  I stopped at Wendy&#8217;s to get lunch,<br />
using the coupon for a free meal I had won from WGRE (thanks, Beth!).</p>
<p>I had made the drive to Chicago about two weeks before.  This<br />
time it took about four hours due to traffic.  We managed to make<br />
it to Jeff&#8217;s house without a problem.  There were oatmeal cookies<br />
waiting for us.  Jeff&#8217;s mom is cool.</p>
<p>I dropped off my two friends and headed into the city to find<br />
Josh&#8217;s apartment.  Apparently, at certain times in the day, They<br />
change the direction of traffic in some lanes.  So a lane that<br />
appears to be going one way is really going the other.  This<br />
explains why I was driving head on towards a fleet of cars.  I<br />
shifted to the far right lane and continued on through the worst<br />
traffic I ever had the misfortune of experiencing.  No one gets<br />
pulled over for speeding in downtown Chicago; it&#8217;s not possible.<br />
Josh somehow secured an apartment a block from the Watertower<br />
in a nice part of town.  I pulled into a parking garage and Josh<br />
was there waiting for me.  We exchanged greetings and headed up<br />
to his apartment.  The place was comfortable (much bigger than a<br />
dorm room).</p>
<p>For dinner, Josh presented me with the best home-made Hawaiian<br />
pizza I have ever had.  Everything about it was right.  Josh has<br />
to make pizza for everyone when he comes back.</p>
<p>We were running late for the concert we were going to, so we<br />
has to jam.  Exiting the apartment, we went across a few blocks<br />
to the elevated train.  I had never been on one, but it was very<br />
much like the subway in New York, only on an elevated track&#8230;<br />
As luck would have it, the stop which would have conveniently<br />
dropped us off in front of the Aragon was closed.  We got off at<br />
the next exit and backtracked through some shady neighborhoods.<br />
I made a mental note not to come back this way after the concert.<br />
After being frisked at the door, we ambled in amongst a large<br />
crowd of concert-goers.  There were a lot of older types there,<br />
which I thought was unusual.  The kids were mostly grunglings and<br />
preppies &#8212; just what you&#8217;d expect at a Toad the Wet Sprocket<br />
concert.  We moved upstairs to the concert floor.  The Aragon is<br />
a converted theater done up to look like a courtyard within the<br />
walls of a Spanish villa.  We were surrounded by towers and<br />
balconies.  Looking up, one saw an artificial night sky complete with stars.</p>
<p>A lot of people were drinking beer when they weren&#8217;t spilling<br />
it all over the floor near where I was standing.  Josh remarked<br />
that it looked like one big party at Delta Upsilon.  He said that<br />
he would feel better if everyone were smoking pot instead of<br />
drinking beer; they&#8217;d be calmer and less pushy.  I agreed.  Later<br />
on, I did observe a group of girls passing a joint amongst themselves.</p>
<p>Hootie and the Blowfish was the band that opened for Toad.  I<br />
had never heard their music, but Ryan seemed to like them, so<br />
that was good enough for me.  Since he was jealous that I was<br />
seeing Hootie AND Toad in the same night, I thought I would<br />
embellish my account of the concert.  But I don&#8217;t have to.<br />
Hootie was amazing.  The lead singer, Darius, had a voice<br />
designed for a gospel choir.  He opened many of the songs <em>a<br />
capella</em>.  Some of them moved me to tears.  After the break, Toad<br />
the Wet Sprocket took the stage.  I had seen them recently with<br />
Ryan, but this performance was at least three times as good.<br />
Darius came out and sang &#8220;Crowing.&#8221;  The second encore was a duet<br />
of Glen and Darius singing &#8220;I Will Not Take These Things For<br />
Granted.&#8221;  All in all, I was pleased.</p>
<p>Josh and I filtered out of the Aragon with everyone else.<br />
Much to our dismay, the place where we exited the el was now<br />
closed.  It was now about 11:30 PM in downtown Chicago.  I turned<br />
to Josh and asked him what we were going to do.  He said that we<br />
could just follow the tracks and get on at the next boarding<br />
point.  This seemed logical to me.  As we walked along the<br />
street, the other concert-goers flagged down cabs and, group by<br />
group, faded away until we were nearly alone.</p>
<p>We made it to the next stop to find that it too was closed.  I<br />
began to get nervous.  I was without my trench coat, so I felt<br />
vulnerable.  I wished I had a gun or a knife, to provide a sense<br />
of security.  All I had was a marble which Brandy had given me<br />
before I left.  Members of Inter Varsity Christian Fellowship gave<br />
out marbles to everyone and told them that they would be praying<br />
for them over break.  I took that marble with me wherever I went<br />
throughout the rest of the week.</p>
<p>I stood there on the dark sidewalk, my hand clutching the<br />
marble in my pocket, looking at Josh.  He said we should keep<br />
following the track.  I looked at how the track ran through a<br />
alley and into darkness further on.  I said, &#8220;Fuck that, Josh.<br />
There&#8217;s no way in hell I&#8217;m going down there.&#8221;  I was really<br />
wigging out.  He assented and we backtracked, looking for an<br />
answer.  Along the way, a legless panhandler rolled up to us<br />
asking for any spare change.  The homeless and the destitute are<br />
hard for me to deal with.  I want to buy them all meals and find<br />
them a place to stay.  I tried that in Ohio and in New York, but<br />
there&#8217;s always more homeless around the corner.  We brushed past<br />
the guy, ignoring him, and something icy prodded my heart.<br />
We finally found an el station and got on board.  There were<br />
two guards with attack dogs on the train to help keep the peace.<br />
I felt safe, but at the same time afraid of a city where such<br />
things were necessary.</p>
<p>Back in Josh&#8217;s apartment, I reveled in the warmth and the<br />
food I had and thought about the guy in the wheelchair.<br />
We checked our e-mail, talked a bit, and then went to sleep.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1995/03/24/spring-break-day-1/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
