<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>computer &#8211; First Time Flowing</title>
	<atom:link href="http://www.andremonserrat.com/tag/computer/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com</link>
	<description>Scattered pages from an apocryphal diary</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 00:04:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.9</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Back from the Dead</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/02/28/back-from-the-dead/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/02/28/back-from-the-dead/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 00:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Geek]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[computer]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=2113</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[This weekend I was going to take my dead computer in to the shop to see what was wrong with it. I decided to plug it in and turn it on just to double check that it didn&#8217;t boot up. But it booted up! It took about 5-10 minutes to boot to Windows. I had [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This weekend I was going to take my dead computer in to the shop to see what was wrong with it. I decided to plug it in and turn it on just to double check that it didn&#8217;t boot up. But it booted up! It took about 5-10 minutes to boot to Windows. I had forgotten how slow it was. Then I moved it and plugged it into the UPS, and it wouldn&#8217;t boot up, just like before. So I plugged it straight into the wall. So I&#8217;m transferring all my files off it now. I think I&#8217;ll try to sell it and put the money towards a new laptop of my own.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/02/28/back-from-the-dead/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stopgap</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/01/06/stopgap/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/01/06/stopgap/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 23:11:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[computer]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=1967</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Whenever money is an obstacle, I often resort to MacGyvering devices together which serve similar purposes to the things I can&#8217;t afford. When I had a house with a large back yard, instead of paying to have the sprinkler system repaired, I jury rigged this elaborate system of hoses and sprinklers all connected to an [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Whenever money is an obstacle, I often resort to MacGyvering devices together which serve similar purposes to the things I can&#8217;t afford. When I had a house with a large back yard, instead of paying to have the sprinkler system repaired, I jury rigged this elaborate system of hoses and sprinklers all connected to an epic foot-long sequence of pressure regulators, adapters and a timer.</p>
<p>Right now I have a few stopgaps of the electronic variety. Instead of getting one of the newer model Time Capsules with dual band and a 2TB hard drive, I have a second router and an external drive working with my older Time Capsule. Instead of one of the new widescreen iMacs as a media center, I have a Mac mini connected to the Time Capsule contraption, routed through a splitter going to a monitor and my HD projector. Instead of my own computer I have this borrowed company laptop running Windows XP and a mishmash of working software and hardware.</p>
<p>But getting by on half-measures is so 2009.</p>
<p>I want 2010 to be a year of simple, efficient connections and elegant solutions. I want fewer things. I want it to just work. I want the tools and means to be transparent. I want acceptable signal to noise ratios. I want beauty and brains and a competitive price point. I want stylish substance. I want to try social without the net and a little more work. I want more hearts and circles and less stars and thumbs ups. I want feeds that feed.</p>
<p>And I want to wave hello&#8230;hello&#8230;hello in a window that never minimizes.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/01/06/stopgap/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>No Photos</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/01/04/no-photos/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/01/04/no-photos/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2010 01:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[What I Did Today]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[computer]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=1963</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[My internet connection and network transfers were crazy slow, so I switched my wireless network over to purely wireless-N. Of course, my iPhone could no longer connect as it was wireless-G. So I found out how to connect my Linksys router to my Time Capsule and have a wireless-G subnetwork. Now everything is fast and [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>My internet connection and network transfers were crazy slow, so I switched my wireless network over to purely wireless-N. Of course, my iPhone could no longer connect as it was wireless-G. So I found out how to connect my Linksys router to my Time Capsule and have a wireless-G subnetwork. Now everything is fast and connected, regardless of protocol.</p>
<p>I have a shelf of art books that I keep meaning to put to use. So today I started with the photography section. I&#8217;m getting re-acquianted with my digital camera, learning what all the functions are. I didn&#8217;t get beyond taking a few test photos, though.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/01/04/no-photos/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
