<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Work &#8211; First Time Flowing</title>
	<atom:link href="http://www.andremonserrat.com/category/life/work-life/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com</link>
	<description>Scattered pages from an apocryphal diary</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 00:04:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.9</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Albuquerque Visit 2011</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2011/12/13/albuquerque-visit-2011/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2011/12/13/albuquerque-visit-2011/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2011 23:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Work]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[oneaday]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://andremonserrat.dreynet.com/?p=2956</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Every year my company flies me back in to Albuquerque for the annual company Christmas party. I usually stay at a nearby motel and work at the main office for a week. This year was wonderfully different as Bess accompanied me. It was great to see her at lunch and have her pick me up [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Every year my company flies me back in to Albuquerque for the annual company Christmas party. I usually stay at a nearby motel and work at the main office for a week. This year was wonderfully different as Bess accompanied me. It was great to see her at lunch and have her pick me up at work instead of returning to a lonely motel room.</p>
<p>As usual, there were a few new faces at work, people who I had only interacted with online. Though I got some things done, I always feel like I get less accomplished when I am in the office than when I am working from home.</p>
<p>When I wasn&#8217;t at work, Bess and I visited some of my old friends, went out to eat, and caught a movie (The Thing) at the dollar theater. The Christmas party was lovely, culminating in the epic gift exchange. Bess picked out a luchador mask and a bobblehead art toy as our contributions. We scored $20 and a remote controlled truck which we donated to a charity (though I kind of wanted to keep the truck).</p>
<p>The travel portion that bookended the trip was a bit taxing, filled with delays and personal discomfort. We were glad to get home.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2011/12/13/albuquerque-visit-2011/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>On Secrets</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2011/01/22/on-secrets/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2011/01/22/on-secrets/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2011 01:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Artwork]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The Stork]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Work]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[oneaday]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=2223</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I was hoping I would be able to share something about a recent project, but it is still under wraps. Stay tuned! I&#8217;m pretty good at keeping secrets. You ask me not to tell, I essentially partition that information away in a special vault in my memory. Eventually even I will be surprised by the [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I was hoping I would be able to share something about a recent project, but it is still under wraps. Stay tuned!</p>
<p>I&#8217;m pretty good at keeping secrets. You ask me not to tell, I essentially partition that information away in a special vault in my memory. Eventually even I will be surprised by the news.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s tricky when I am working on something cool, but I&#8217;m forbidden to show anyone. I recently had to sign an NDA at work. Now I belong to a secret society who know about *It*.</p>
<p>In other news, I have secured three video testimonials about The Stork. I want to get one more and then cut together a promo video so I can launch the Kickstarter project. I&#8217;d like to get that going by the end of the month.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2011/01/22/on-secrets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Don&#8217;t Know Whether I&#8217;m the Boxer or the Bag</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/06/15/dont-know-whether-im-the-boxer-or-the-bag/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/06/15/dont-know-whether-im-the-boxer-or-the-bag/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2010 02:34:18 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Work]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=2148</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I scarcely know how to hold a pen, so long has it been since I pressed one to parchment. My desk and all its contents were claimed by the waves, repurposed as a piscine mansion. Ink is dear, gleaned from a painstaking process involving the crushed seeds of a peculiar mango-shaped fruit we discovered. And [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I scarcely know how to hold a pen, so long has it been<br />
since I pressed one to parchment. My desk and all its contents were<br />
claimed by the waves, repurposed as a piscine mansion. Ink is dear,<br />
gleaned from a painstaking process involving the crushed seeds of a<br />
peculiar mango-shaped fruit we discovered. And I wonder if the<br />
letters will last. Work on the ship continues apace. The command<br />
center and galley receive most of our attention and it is generally<br />
agreed that the day these rooms become a place of respite rather<br />
than labor will be sweet indeed. My constitution continues its<br />
decline, constantly embattled from all sides by the heavy vapors<br />
enclosing us. The breathing apparatus and the seltzers have proven<br />
ineffective. I spend most days on the other side of the thick<br />
acrylic bubbles, overseeing the work, sparing an occasional glance<br />
out at the oppressive topography. But I have begun to feel it even<br />
in my cabin, lying on my bunk. Some spectre leeches my strength, so<br />
that I waken not refreshed, but burdened. The daily job manifests<br />
from the investors blur together. Each site survey has become an<br />
iteration of the previous one, permutations of some ur-site<br />
unfolding through time and space, like hundreds of incrementally<br />
flawed daisies. I send the drones their orders, instruction sets I<br />
know by heart. I fear for the day when I see a colleague insert the<br />
control cards and my own legs lurch forward, watching helpless as<br />
my hands reach for the drill.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/06/15/dont-know-whether-im-the-boxer-or-the-bag/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Achievement Unlocked</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/02/18/achievement-unlocked/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/02/18/achievement-unlocked/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2010 01:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Artwork]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Board Games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[House of Whack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Something Real]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Video Games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Work]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=2092</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Sometimes I fall into that slough of self-examination where I feel as though I have accomplished nothing with my life. Or, when compared to Person X, I am found wanting. This often happens when I&#8217;m not currently working on a creative project, as they tend to define me and give me purpose. So I think [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sometimes I fall into that slough of self-examination where I feel as though I have accomplished nothing with my life. Or, when compared to Person X, I am found wanting. This often happens when I&#8217;m not currently working on a creative project, as they tend to define me and give me purpose.</p>
<p>So I think it might be helpful to recollect the things I <em>have</em> achieved. Not in a boastful, resting on my laurels sort of way. But to remind myself that I am the same person who did all of those things. Try it yourself when you are feeling somewhat less than.<span id="more-2092"></span></p>
<p>Here are some of the things I have accomplished so far:</p>
<ol>
<li>Learned to program in BASIC when I was 8 years old</li>
<li>Wrote a computer game when I was 10 and sold one copy</li>
<li>Learned to ride a bike</li>
<li>Learned to play the trombone</li>
<li>Wrote and directed <em>Welcome to the Real World</em> during my senior year of high school</li>
<li>Wrote and performed skits and monologues in front of hundreds of people</li>
<li>Learned to drive a stick shift</li>
<li>Was class Treasurer and class Chaplain</li>
<li>Was a National Merit Scholar</li>
<li>Read the entire Bible</li>
<li>Graduated high school</li>
<li>Won best supporting actor for my performance in <em>Off Kennedy&#8217;s Yacht</em></li>
<li>Won best playwright for <em>All We See and Seem</em></li>
<li>Helped make the short film <em>K</em></li>
<li>Wrote a thesis on Interactive Fiction</li>
<li>Ran a massively multiplayer interactive fiction game as my senior writing project in college</li>
<li>Saw Pink Floyd in concert</li>
<li>Drove across the U.S. both East to West and North to South</li>
<li>Learned how to build my own computer</li>
<li>Filmed, directed and edited the documentary <em>Goodbye, Hello</em></li>
<li>Graduated college</li>
<li>Survived six car accidents, unscathed</li>
<li>Convinced someone to marry me</li>
<li>Created presentations for the biggest company on earth</li>
<li>Owned a house</li>
<li>Survived a divorce</li>
<li>Taught myself Photoshop, Dreamweaver, Flash, Poser, Illustrator, Premiere, and After Effects</li>
<li>Won a short fiction contest with my story <em>The Numbers Game</em></li>
<li>Published a chapbook of poetry called <em>Poem-Shaped Lies</em></li>
<li>Solved <em>Myst III</em> without any hints</li>
<li>Adapted <em>The Warlock of Firetop Mountain</em> into a module for Neverwinter Nights. It won a contest created by the publishers of the book. (The British) Steve Jackson played it and wrote me a letter of congratulations.</li>
<li>Checked in to a mental institution</li>
<li>Checked out of a mental institution</li>
<li>Made love to beautiful women</li>
<li>Stood naked on top of a volcano</li>
<li>Adopted a pregnant cat</li>
<li>Won a Telly award for my piece on the New Mexico Jazz Workshop</li>
<li>Had a crisis of faith</li>
<li>Learned how to break up with girls</li>
<li>Dual-wielded .45mm pistols</li>
<li>Published another chapbook of poetry called <em>From the Ashes of Puppets</em></li>
<li>Won a fiction contest with my story <em>My Strychnine Valentine</em></li>
<li>Sued the DEA and won</li>
<li>Learned how to make friends in a new city</li>
<li>Lived in at least 9 different cities</li>
<li>Performed slam poetry in five major cities</li>
<li>Created and published a board game called <em>House of Whack</em></li>
<li>Created a web comic called <em>Dream Job</em></li>
<li>Held my own with John Hodgman</li>
<li>Was a guest columnist for Secure Immaturity</li>
<li>Created and organized a film festival for women filmmakers called <em>Something Real</em></li>
<li>Learned how to practice authenticity and integrity</li>
<li>Helped create a bumper for Fantastic Fest called <em>Lollipop</em></li>
<li>Created a board game and beer meetup called <em>Boards &#8216;N Brews</em></li>
<li>Performed improv comedy</li>
<li>Had an existential crisis</li>
<li>Beat Mischa in Wiz-War</li>
<li>Published <em>The Stork</em></li>
<li>Filed my taxes in January</li>
<li>Saw the last night launch of a space shuttle</li>
<li>Designed hundreds of web sites</li>
<li>Avoided ever breaking any bones in my body</li>
<li>Have, at one time or another, lost everything I thought I needed to survive</li>
<li>Did what was right instead of what was easy</li>
</ol>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/02/18/achievement-unlocked/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Every Day the Same Dream</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/02/04/every-day-the-same-dream/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/02/04/every-day-the-same-dream/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2010 04:41:10 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Work]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=2058</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Work has been really stressful the past few weeks. Every day it feels like I have survived a battle. My inbox has become a hydra of tasks. I cut one down and two more rise in its place.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Work has been really stressful the past few weeks. Every day it feels like I have survived a battle. My inbox has become a hydra of tasks. I cut one down and two more rise in its place.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/02/04/every-day-the-same-dream/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inundated</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/01/19/inundated/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/01/19/inundated/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2010 03:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Work]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=2015</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Yesterday there were 15 new emails in my work inbox, which is a lot for the morning. I literally spent all day going through them and resolving each issue, even as more emails came in. Today was similar, but the emails were spread throughout the day. Each one a new wasp to add to the [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Yesterday there were 15 new emails in my work inbox, which is a lot for the morning. I literally spent all day going through them and resolving each issue, even as more emails came in. Today was similar, but the emails were spread throughout the day. Each one a new wasp to add to the constant swarm of things that needed to be done. Somehow I managed to get a couple of web sites finished too. I&#8217;m the Scotty of web design, working miracles all by myself.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/01/19/inundated/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
