<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	
	>
<channel>
	<title>Comments on: An Analogy</title>
	<atom:link href="http://www.andremonserrat.com/2005/12/09/an-analogy/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2005/12/09/an-analogy/</link>
	<description>Scattered pages from an apocryphal diary</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 12:42:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.9</generator>
	<item>
		<title>By: Monica</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2005/12/09/an-analogy/#comment-106</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Monica]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2005 00:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://andremonserrat.dreynet.com/2005/12/09/an-analogy/#comment-106</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[might I hesitate a thought?  That perhaps loving a unicorn is never wrong...that love in it&#039;s truest form is never wrong.  That you can never really &quot;get rid&quot; of love if it is true, but only change it through transmutation (something of a alchemist in us).  But perhaps where the trouble lies is in expecting that a unicorn might change to keep your love, or assuming that they can.  Or of wanting to keep a unicorn.  But perhaps I&#039;m the wrong girl to ask, as when I watch Legend, I empathize most with the dark Lily who sits beside big D... but that&#039;s just the side of me that hates unicorns because she once wanted to touch one.I also read a good book many years ago called The Unicorn Creed, and it had a lovely discussion of the ugly and foolish sides of some unicorns... maybe you should read that one...]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>might I hesitate a thought?  That perhaps loving a unicorn is never wrong&#8230;that love in it&#8217;s truest form is never wrong.  That you can never really &#8220;get rid&#8221; of love if it is true, but only change it through transmutation (something of a alchemist in us).  But perhaps where the trouble lies is in expecting that a unicorn might change to keep your love, or assuming that they can.  Or of wanting to keep a unicorn.  But perhaps I&#8217;m the wrong girl to ask, as when I watch Legend, I empathize most with the dark Lily who sits beside big D&#8230; but that&#8217;s just the side of me that hates unicorns because she once wanted to touch one.I also read a good book many years ago called The Unicorn Creed, and it had a lovely discussion of the ugly and foolish sides of some unicorns&#8230; maybe you should read that one&#8230;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>By: The "Lamper"</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2005/12/09/an-analogy/#comment-107</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[The "Lamper"]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2005 20:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://andremonserrat.dreynet.com/2005/12/09/an-analogy/#comment-107</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[nooooo be strong Drey b stronggggggg!!!! :)]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>nooooo be strong Drey b stronggggggg!!!! 🙂</p>
]]></content:encoded>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
