<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Books &#8211; First Time Flowing</title>
	<atom:link href="http://www.andremonserrat.com/category/geek/books-geek/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com</link>
	<description>Scattered pages from an apocryphal diary</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 00:04:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.9</generator>
	<item>
		<title>An Embarrassment of Riches</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2011/09/04/an-embarrassment-of-riches/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2011/09/04/an-embarrassment-of-riches/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2011 00:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Anime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Board Games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Movies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[RPGs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Video Games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[oneaday]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://andremonserrat.dreynet.com/?p=2886</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I may have mentioned this before, but there are too many things. And by &#8220;things&#8221; I mean books, video games, movies, TV shows, board games, songs, apps, and any other media one might experience. Right now, today, there are probably more things that I&#8217;d like to have a look at than I have time remaining [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I may have mentioned this before, but there are too many things. And by &#8220;things&#8221; I mean books, video games, movies, TV shows, board games, songs, apps, and any other media one might experience. Right now, today, there are probably more things that I&#8217;d like to have a look at than I have time remaining in my life to do so. And tomorrow, someone will add even more.</p>
<p>I don&#8217;t like to leave things unfinished, no loose ends. But now I have this frayed blanket of partially read books, half-watched shows, unfinished video games, barely messed with apps, and board games still in shrink wrap. At one point these things were rare and hard won. As a child I created an impromptu garage sale to fund the purchase of the BattleTech board game, shutting the sale down the moment I could afford to buy. And then I played BattleTech for ages. Now everything is so easy to obtain, effortlessly plucked from the ether. But I feel like it takes a greater force of will to slow down and appreciate a single thing, knowing there are thousands more awaiting my attention. It is like touring the Louvre in a formula one race car.</p>
<p>I&#8217;ve decided I need to shift my perception of all this media, or at least to try. I&#8217;m trying to see it as another planetary ecosystem, something vast and ever present. In the same way that I do not need to play with every breed of dog on the planet, I do not need to play every game. If I see one I like, I will pet it and enjoy that moment. I&#8217;m really happy just knowing that all those things are out there and that sometimes my path will intersect with some of them.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2011/09/04/an-embarrassment-of-riches/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Could He Be the One?</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/02/20/could-he-be-the-one/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/02/20/could-he-be-the-one/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2010 05:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Movies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[What I Did Today]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=2096</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Recently I decided to try reading the the Dune books in chronological order, including the extended universe books by Brian Herbert and Kevin J. Anderson. I made it about 100 or so pages into the Butlerian Jihad before I couldn&#8217;t stand it. The story seemed epic and could have been interesting, but the writing was [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Recently I decided to try reading the the Dune books in chronological order, including the extended universe books by Brian Herbert and Kevin J. Anderson. I made it about 100 or so pages into the Butlerian Jihad before I couldn&#8217;t stand it. The story seemed epic and could have been interesting, but the writing was just so juvenile I couldn&#8217;t justify spending more time in the series.</p>
<p>So I satisfied my Dune craving by rewatching the Dune Extended Edition with Nick and Amanda. Despite the horribly dated effects, it is still awesome.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/02/20/could-he-be-the-one/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Neverending Story</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/01/20/the-neverending-story/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/01/20/the-neverending-story/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 05:09:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[What I Did Today]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=2017</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I&#8217;m re-reading the Neverending Story, which is a bit of a misnomer because I apparently came to its end at some point in the past. I don&#8217;t know if all editions of the book are as meta as the one I own. The text alternates between maroon and green ink, just like the book in [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;m re-reading the Neverending Story, which is a bit of a misnomer because I apparently came to its end at some point in the past. I don&#8217;t know if all editions of the book are as meta as the one I own. The text alternates between maroon and green ink, just like the book in the story, indicating which parts are from the book Bastian is reading and which are Bastian&#8217;s outside world. And it also has these great full-page illustrations for the first letter of each chapter, which happen to go through the entire alphabet, A to Z, just like the &#8220;real&#8221; book. I haven&#8217;t tried yelling out &#8220;Moon Child&#8221; to see if I am swept off to a fantasy realm of luck dragons and rock biters.</p>
<p>I first read it some time after seeing the movie as a child. I was as engrossed in the tale as Bastian. Indeed, I even got hungry when Bastian did and felt what he felt. I was enraptured with the thought of magical books that were somehow aware of their readers and could change over time. I imagined how I could create such a book. I remember becoming interested in finding just the right sort of blank book with properly enchanted paper stock.</p>
<p>The movie is a fairly faithful adaptation of the first half of the book. What the movie doesn&#8217;t tell you is that after he saves Fantastica (or Fantasia, as it is called in the film) from the Nothing, Bastian becomes a mostly pompous dick. At least at the part I&#8217;m at now. He has the power to remake the world as he sees fit and he sets himself up as a total badass with ultimate authority over all he sees. I&#8217;m assuming this is all leading to a lesson in staying true to yourself.</p>
<p>In other news, I attended a writer&#8217;s meetup. Again, I&#8217;m getting out, meeting new people with whom I might have something in common. We met at a coffee house and read brief excerpts from three of the attendees. This was followed by a round of constructive criticism. I managed to stave off an entirely judgmental attitude and contributed suggestions that were well received. Perhaps I am growing as a person. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/11/72x72/1f609.png" alt="😉" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2010/01/20/the-neverending-story/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Lathe of Heaven</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2009/09/11/the-lathe-of-heaven/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2009/09/11/the-lathe-of-heaven/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2009 03:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reft]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=1935</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I guess this&#8217;ll teach me not to read &#8220;The Invisibles&#8221; and &#8220;The Lathe of Heaven&#8221; simultaneously while having an existential crisis. The language is always going to be an issue. As I learned from The Invisibles, we&#8217;ve only been taught half the letters of the true alphabet. This entire experience is created in language and [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I guess this&#8217;ll teach me not to read &#8220;The Invisibles&#8221; and &#8220;The Lathe of Heaven&#8221; simultaneously while having an existential crisis.</p>
<p>The language is always going to be an issue. As I learned from The Invisibles, we&#8217;ve only been taught half the letters of the true alphabet. This entire experience is created in language and there are things I have no words for.<span id="more-1935"></span></p>
<p>What I&#8217;ve learned from conversations and responses to my inquiry &#8220;Why are you doing this?&#8221; is that, to various extents, we are all making this up as we go along. We have constructed customized realities, an elaborate latticework of experiences, ideas, and feelings. Parts of these realities are attached to fixtures seemingly independent, though we have also created those fixtures (but have forgotten, forsaken, distanced ourselves from them).</p>
<p>We seek out consensus to reinforce and reaffirm. Each module of the reality, or each &#8220;fact&#8221;, varies in the amount of consensus needed and this also varies from person to person. Many modules have so much consensus that they give the appearance of being factory installed. This is the realm of macro-level concepts like physics and social mores. Heavy consensus modules require little effort from the individual. So many people believe in the thoughtform that only a tiny processing cycle per person is required to maintain it. These thoughtforms appear inflexible and unassailable.</p>
<p>In isolation, away from consensus, rogue realities flourish. This isolation is also rooted in some inaccessibility of language: the newborn, the person in a foreign country, the person stranded on an island, the child born deaf, blind and mute. What would your reality look like if stripped of consensus? If you could invent new words because it didn&#8217;t occur to you that it &#8220;just wasn&#8217;t done&#8221;? There seem to be so many wonderful things in the realm of low-consensus thoughtforms. Cats share wisdom, pots boil when you look away, stars grant wishes, and real love only needs one person to believe in it.</p>
<p>I kept hearing people say variations of &#8220;This is what feels right to me.&#8221; They had invented purpose for their life and given themselves tools to measure it. But it isn&#8217;t usually described that way. There are always these pre-existing tools. There are outside influences. There is a need to distance oneself from from these other factors in order to validate the whole arrangement. We need something that is Not Us. But I think these pre-existing circumstances are invented as well. It is a conspiracy of dissociated terrorist architects. Ask all the ants how the anthill got there and each will point at the other ants. It&#8217;s a paradox.</p>
<p>I also kept getting &#8220;Make your own meaning.&#8221; I think I&#8217;m afraid to. I think it might be lonely. And it lead to a thought that I&#8217;m still trying to get a handle on: If we&#8217;re inventing reality on our own terms and part of that involves creating forces in opposition to us (challenges, measurements, shadows, counterbalance), then the things that are &#8220;false&#8221; about us (&#8220;You&#8217;re not smart enough&#8221;, &#8220;You&#8217;re not a good musician&#8221;, &#8220;You will never find true love&#8221;) are actually true. If we think we need them to be.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2009/09/11/the-lathe-of-heaven/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>9</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Untethered</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2009/06/19/untethered/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2009/06/19/untethered/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2009 22:23:43 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Movies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Video Games]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=1850</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[My project to slough off all the excess stuff in my life continues. My music collection has been digital for years, save for a few collectibles and albums by friends. I&#8217;ve gotten my DVD collection down to about 17 boxes. Out of print films that you can&#8217;t get on Netflix. So I&#8217;m no longer buying [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>My project to slough off all the excess stuff in my life continues.</p>
<p>My music collection has been digital for years, save for a few collectibles and albums by friends. I&#8217;ve gotten my DVD collection down to about 17 boxes. Out of print films that you can&#8217;t get on Netflix. So I&#8217;m no longer buying movies of the common variety.</p>
<p>I don&#8217;t have very many video games either. When I finish a game or get bored with it, I sell it. I just signed up for GameFly, so I will never buy another video game unless it falls into the small, evergreen category where Rock Band resides.</p>
<p>Movies and games are both heading into an all-digital delivery system. There are many reasons for this, but a big one for the publishers is that the secondhand market will die. You can&#8217;t resell your digital copy of The Dark Knight to someone on Amazon. GameStop will eventually become a store for classic used games from the 2000s. One day it will seem ridiculous that digital information was bonded to physical platters and cartridges.</p>
<p>I&#8217;ve thinned down my book collection to two small book shelves. As I finish books, I&#8217;ll sell them to Half Price Books or give them away. Again, I&#8217;m only going to be purchasing hard to find items or books which make practical sense to own. I converted a majority of my Amazon book wish list over to a reading list for my brand new account at the Austin Public Library system. Holy shit, is this a slick operation! The online catalog system is robust. I can have books held and delivered to my local branch. I only stumped the system once or twice whilst searching for graphic novels. Their collection of every series I care about is comprehensive. They even had a copy of the out of print Encyclopedia of Fantastic Victoriana, which is basically steampunk porn. All for free. Why didn&#8217;t I do this sooner? Also, if there is a Kindle version of a book available, I&#8217;ll buy that over the dead tree version. The Kindle iPhone app is actually pretty great and I&#8217;ve been enjoying 20,000 Leagues Under the Sea on it.</p>
<p>The board game collection remains pretty large. I&#8217;ll probably thin it down over the course of a few years, getting rid of the so-so games, keeping only the ones I truly love.</p>
<p>I&#8217;ve also been untethering my online life. I&#8217;ve moved more and more documents up into the cloud so I can access them from anywhere. I stopped using desktop clients for mail, scheduling, spreadsheets, and twittering. It&#8217;s all web-based now. I can do all of my communication from anywhere. It feels good to shut my computer down when I&#8217;m done working instead of having to check in on it for new messages.</p>
<p>My iPhone is proving more and more invaluable. Today I set up a wireless storage app so I can keep my writing and important documents backed up on a password protected micro web server. It&#8217;s like having a magic extradimensional 16GB pocket I can reach into at any time.</p>
<p>When I can afford it, I&#8217;ll probably replace my computer with a laptop. I like the idea of being able to grab a backpack and take off, bringing my entire world with me.</p>
<p>I feel lighter.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2009/06/19/untethered/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>3</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Too Many Socks</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2009/04/01/too-many-socks/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2009/04/01/too-many-socks/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2009 20:52:52 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Movies]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=1709</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I just realized that the main reason I still have DVDs and books is so that other people can look at them and make a judgment about how awesome I am. They are decorative. This is the age of Netflix and Amazon. I don&#8217;t need all those things taking up space. Rare is the time [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I just realized that the main reason I still have DVDs and books is so that other people can look at them and make a judgment about how awesome I am. They are decorative. This is the age of Netflix and Amazon. I don&#8217;t <em>need</em> all those things taking up space. Rare is the time when I absolutely must watch a particular film immediately. And being such a slow reader, I doubt I will be re-reading anything any time soon.</p>
<p>So I&#8217;m going to liquidate all my DVDs and books that aren&#8217;t rare or hard to get. I&#8217;m tired of dragging them around. If people need to know the movies and books I like, they can check any number of online sources.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2009/04/01/too-many-socks/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Interworld</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/01/01/interworld/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/01/01/interworld/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2008 04:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Top Ten Books]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/01/01/interworld/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Although the cover says the book was written by Neil Gaiman and Micheal Reaves, I will be filing this one under &#8220;R&#8221;. 1. Interworld 2. 3. 4. 5. 6. 7. 8. 9. 10.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Although the cover says the book was written by Neil Gaiman and Micheal Reaves, I will be filing this one under &#8220;R&#8221;.</p>
<p>1. Interworld<br />
2.<br />
3.<br />
4.<br />
5.<br />
6.<br />
7.<br />
8.<br />
9.<br />
10.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/01/01/interworld/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Free Books</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/01/01/free-books/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/01/01/free-books/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2008 02:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Activity Report]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/01/01/free-books/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[For today&#8217;s activity, I established a small collection of books to give away/push off on friends who visit. These include some science fiction novels, graphic design books, graphic novels, books on writing and etcetera, etcetera. So, if you come over, please peruse the books and take something.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For today&#8217;s activity, I established a small collection of books to give away/push off on friends who visit. These include some science fiction novels, graphic design books, graphic novels, books on writing and etcetera, etcetera.</p>
<p>So, if you come over, please peruse the books and take something.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2008/01/01/free-books/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Books I Read in 1997</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1998/01/01/books-i-read-in-1997/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1998/01/01/books-i-read-in-1997/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1998 14:27:45 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Books]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=1893</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[( 2.3 Books/Month Average) 1. The Handmaid’s Tale 2. Something Wicked This Way Comes 3. Sandman: The Wake 4. Chaos &#38; Cyberculture 5. Over Sea, Under Stone 6. The Ascent of Wonder 7. The Dark is Rising 8. Greenwitch 9. The Grey King 10. Love for a Lifetime 11. Silver on the Tree 12. The [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>( 2.3 Books/Month Average)<br />
1.	The Handmaid’s Tale<br />
2.	Something Wicked This Way Comes<br />
3.	Sandman: The Wake<br />
4.	Chaos &amp; Cyberculture<br />
5.	Over Sea, Under Stone<br />
6.	The Ascent of Wonder<br />
7.	The Dark is Rising<br />
8.	Greenwitch<br />
9.	The Grey King<br />
10.	Love for a Lifetime<br />
11.	Silver on the Tree<br />
12.	The Book of Three<br />
13.	The Black Cauldron<br />
14.	The Castle of Llyr<br />
15.	Taran Wanderer<br />
16.	Books of Magic<br />
17.	The High King<br />
18.	Signal to Noise<br />
19.	The Foundling and Other Tales of Prydain<br />
20.	Sandman Midnight Theatre<br />
21.	Death: The Time of Your Life<br />
22.	Black Orchid<br />
23.	The Day I Swapped My Dad for Two Goldfish<br />
24.	On Cats and Dogs<br />
25.	Dandelion Wine<br />
26.	Neverwhere<br />
27.	Don’t Panic<br />
28.	Permutation City</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1998/01/01/books-i-read-in-1997/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Books I Read in 1996</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1997/01/01/books-i-read-in-1996/</link>
		<comments>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1997/01/01/books-i-read-in-1996/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 1997 14:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Books]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.andremonserrat.com/?p=1891</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[( 4.7 Books/Month Average) 1. Understanding Comics 2. Dinotopia 3. The New Hugo Winners 4. Sandman: Preludes &#38; Nocturnes 5. Sandman: The Doll’s House 6. The Big Time 7. Sandman: Dream Country 8. Sandman: Season of Mists 9. Sandman: Fables &#38; Reflections 10. Faust Part I 11. Sandman: A Game of You 12. Death: The [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>( 4.7 Books/Month Average)<br />
1. Understanding Comics<br />
2. Dinotopia<br />
3. The New Hugo Winners<br />
4. Sandman: Preludes &amp; Nocturnes<br />
5. Sandman: The Doll’s House<br />
6. The Big Time<br />
7. Sandman: Dream Country<br />
8. Sandman: Season of Mists<br />
9. Sandman: Fables &amp; Reflections<br />
10. Faust Part I<br />
11. Sandman: A Game of You<br />
12. Death: The High Cost of Living<br />
13. Sandman: Brief Lives<br />
14. One<br />
15. Sandman: World’s End<br />
16. Crazy in Alabama<br />
17. The Book of Answers<br />
18. The Last Unicorn<br />
19. How to Write Science Fiction and Fantasy<br />
20. Violent Cases<br />
21. Will You Please Be Quiet, Please?<br />
22. Vurt<br />
23. The Once and Future King<br />
24. The Book of Merlyn<br />
25. Pollen<br />
26. The Artificial Kid<br />
27. Schismatrix<br />
28. Crystal Express<br />
29. Naked Lunch<br />
30. Generation of Swine<br />
31. Islands in the Net<br />
32. Sandman: The Kindly Ones<br />
33. Globalhead<br />
34. Heavy Weather<br />
35. The Difference Engine<br />
36. Hamlet<br />
37. Han Solo at Star’s End<br />
38. The Great Shark Hunt<br />
39. Han Solo’s Revenge<br />
40. Han Solo and the Lost Legacy<br />
41. Finding the Love of Your Life<br />
42. A New Hope<br />
43. The Empire Strikes Back<br />
44. Songs of the Doomed<br />
45. Couplehood<br />
46. Shadows of the Empire<br />
47. Automated Alice<br />
48. Cinderella (Wegman)<br />
49. Return of the Jedi<br />
50. Holy Fire<br />
51. The Hacker Crackdown<br />
52. Idoru<br />
53. The Master’s Gambit<br />
54. The Working Woman’s Wedding Planner<br />
55. Before the Invid Storm<br />
56. How to Draw a Radish</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.andremonserrat.com/1997/01/01/books-i-read-in-1996/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
