<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	
	>
<channel>
	<title>Comments on: One is the Lonliest Number</title>
	<atom:link href="http://www.andremonserrat.com/2005/12/29/one-is-the-lonliest-number/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2005/12/29/one-is-the-lonliest-number/</link>
	<description>Scattered pages from an apocryphal diary</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 12:42:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.9</generator>
	<item>
		<title>By: Monica</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2005/12/29/one-is-the-lonliest-number/#comment-109</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Monica]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2005 18:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://andremonserrat.dreynet.com/2005/12/29/one-is-the-lonliest-number/#comment-109</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Hey drey, know what you mean. I&#039;m going to throw a little &quot;polyanna&quot; in there for ya (perhaps it&#039;s because I&#039;m sleep deprived that I can maintain the optimism), but perhaps the digital world allows us to transcend spacial boundaries so as to find a much better fit of a tribe for all of us.  Back in the day we may have been limited to the direct people we were in physical proximity to.  I shudder to think about having to pick someone to get married to in the town I grew up in at this point, or having my friends limited to their number.  The only problem is that we find our &quot;right&quot; tribe, but we are then missing the physical necessity of proximity to other humans that comes with being a collective.  We get a super big bonus, but also a large drawback that I think maybe we have to figure out how to solve.  (and BTW, I think our anonymous friend should learn how to spell before they get all high and mighty:)]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hey drey, know what you mean. I&#8217;m going to throw a little &#8220;polyanna&#8221; in there for ya (perhaps it&#8217;s because I&#8217;m sleep deprived that I can maintain the optimism), but perhaps the digital world allows us to transcend spacial boundaries so as to find a much better fit of a tribe for all of us.  Back in the day we may have been limited to the direct people we were in physical proximity to.  I shudder to think about having to pick someone to get married to in the town I grew up in at this point, or having my friends limited to their number.  The only problem is that we find our &#8220;right&#8221; tribe, but we are then missing the physical necessity of proximity to other humans that comes with being a collective.  We get a super big bonus, but also a large drawback that I think maybe we have to figure out how to solve.  (and BTW, I think our anonymous friend should learn how to spell before they get all high and mighty:)</p>
]]></content:encoded>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>By: Anonymous</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2005/12/29/one-is-the-lonliest-number/#comment-110</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anonymous]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2005 13:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://andremonserrat.dreynet.com/2005/12/29/one-is-the-lonliest-number/#comment-110</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[self rigthtoues quasi intelectual reaping what you are sowing]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>self rigthtoues quasi intelectual reaping what you are sowing</p>
]]></content:encoded>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
