<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	
	>
<channel>
	<title>Comments on: 42 Again</title>
	<atom:link href="http://www.andremonserrat.com/2011/04/23/42-again/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2011/04/23/42-again/</link>
	<description>Scattered pages from an apocryphal diary</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 12:42:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.9</generator>
	<item>
		<title>By: Pombroll</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2011/04/23/42-again/#comment-694</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pombroll]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 19:49:36 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://andremonserrat.dreynet.com/?p=2768#comment-694</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I believe you gave a proper response to the person who posted an anonymous comment. I&#039;m sure your topic is beyond my pay grade. But, I&#039;ll try to do a little better than the poor fellow above.

There are no two humans who are igual. Even identical twins are different. Yet, we are pressured by culture, lnaguage, ideology, etc. to follow the &quot;Herd mentality.&quot; Political correctness is part of fitting in.

My take is that there is one universe within each of us, and that universe grows from the inside out: The less you depend on outside sources, the freer you are. Complete freedom is only achieved when you become king of your own universe.

You do not feel &quot;Settled&quot; because you are trying to please masters outside you, to utter the PC sentiment, when such sentiment does not fit your universe.

Richard Dawkins is well known for his belief that we are the roots produced by our genes, taking a mechanistic approach, as T.H. Huxley, to explain away morality. However, his attack on God is only a distraction because whether or not Gods esists, does not solve the issue of where morality comes from.

There people a lot smarter than I am, such as President Obama, who believes in &quot;Collective Salvation&quot; rather than in individual salvation. That is more in line with his Socialist ideology than with reality. If there is a God, equality in mankind would be his mantra. Yet, each one of us is unique. My take is that we have to grow the God inside us until we feel free to act God-like.]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I believe you gave a proper response to the person who posted an anonymous comment. I&#8217;m sure your topic is beyond my pay grade. But, I&#8217;ll try to do a little better than the poor fellow above.</p>
<p>There are no two humans who are igual. Even identical twins are different. Yet, we are pressured by culture, lnaguage, ideology, etc. to follow the &#8220;Herd mentality.&#8221; Political correctness is part of fitting in.</p>
<p>My take is that there is one universe within each of us, and that universe grows from the inside out: The less you depend on outside sources, the freer you are. Complete freedom is only achieved when you become king of your own universe.</p>
<p>You do not feel &#8220;Settled&#8221; because you are trying to please masters outside you, to utter the PC sentiment, when such sentiment does not fit your universe.</p>
<p>Richard Dawkins is well known for his belief that we are the roots produced by our genes, taking a mechanistic approach, as T.H. Huxley, to explain away morality. However, his attack on God is only a distraction because whether or not Gods esists, does not solve the issue of where morality comes from.</p>
<p>There people a lot smarter than I am, such as President Obama, who believes in &#8220;Collective Salvation&#8221; rather than in individual salvation. That is more in line with his Socialist ideology than with reality. If there is a God, equality in mankind would be his mantra. Yet, each one of us is unique. My take is that we have to grow the God inside us until we feel free to act God-like.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>By: Drey</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2011/04/23/42-again/#comment-689</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 20:24:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://andremonserrat.dreynet.com/?p=2768#comment-689</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The person who wrote this ignorant bullshit is a coward. It is really easy to sit there in the library and post completely anonymous comments. You aren&#039;t interested in a dialog or treating me like a person. You just care about your agenda. &lt;em&gt;That&lt;/em&gt; is selfish and lazy.]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The person who wrote this ignorant bullshit is a coward. It is really easy to sit there in the library and post completely anonymous comments. You aren&#8217;t interested in a dialog or treating me like a person. You just care about your agenda. <em>That</em> is selfish and lazy.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>By: Unknown</title>
		<link>http://www.andremonserrat.com/2011/04/23/42-again/#comment-688</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Unknown]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 20:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://andremonserrat.dreynet.com/?p=2768#comment-688</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Not settled?
Try lazy
It takes work/faith to find the real truth you are looking for in Messiah Jesus.
Try also being a coward
It takes being bold to kick out the dark ones attached to some of your parts.
If other multiples can do it so can you.]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Not settled?<br />
Try lazy<br />
It takes work/faith to find the real truth you are looking for in Messiah Jesus.<br />
Try also being a coward<br />
It takes being bold to kick out the dark ones attached to some of your parts.<br />
If other multiples can do it so can you.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
