<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Music &#8211; DreamPunk Productions</title>
	<atom:link href="http://www.dreampunk.com/category/music/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://www.dreampunk.com</link>
	<description>Game and story-shaped designs</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 20:51:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.9</generator>
	<item>
		<title>March Marches On</title>
		<link>http://www.dreampunk.com/2010/03/04/march-marches-on/</link>
		<comments>http://www.dreampunk.com/2010/03/04/march-marches-on/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2010 04:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The Stork]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://dreampunk.dreynet.com/2010/03/04/march-marches-on/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[So, starting tomorrow, my Google calendar looks like a blocky cross section of the Funtime Mountains or the EEG readout of the Busytown heartbeat. Lots going on. Planned soirées and the like. It resembles a social person&#8217;s schedule, as opposed to a Netflix hermit. Tomorrow night is the STAPLE pre-party at Austin Books and Comics. I&#8217;m going [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>So, starting tomorrow, my Google calendar looks like a blocky cross section of the Funtime Mountains or the EEG readout of the Busytown heartbeat. Lots going on. Planned soirées and the like. It resembles a <em>social </em>person&#8217;s schedule, as opposed to a Netflix hermit.<span id="more-68"></span></p>
<p>Tomorrow night is the STAPLE pre-party at Austin Books and Comics. I&#8217;m going to roll in there like I know what is going on. But I don&#8217;t know what to say to a room full of indie comic writers. I&#8217;ll hang out there until I feel awkward and then bounce over to Reed and Laura Lee&#8217;s housewarming party.</p>
<p>Saturday is all about STAPLE. Got to get up early, drag some products over to the convention center, check in, find my table and act like I know what I am doing. My plan is to set up House of Whack and invite people to play. Also, I will trick people into paying $1 for The Stork when it is actually worth $1.45! Ha ha! No idea what to expect. I&#8217;ve never done an expo for reals and I don&#8217;t know if I can deal with sitting at a booth all day.</p>
<p>After that, there are several events that I will attempt to hit, depending on my energy level. My friend Jonathan is having a birthday party, there is the STAPLE BBQ dinner and the STAPLE after party. It will be at a club with a DJ, so I don&#8217;t know.</p>
<p>Sunday evening brings Fiction Circus. It&#8217;s a thing.</p>
<p>Monday = take a breath.</p>
<p>Tuesday is Boards &#8216;N Brews. That night&#8217;s double feature is Dungeon Lords and Cosmic Encounter.</p>
<p>Wednesday = dork around online.</p>
<p>Thursday promises an interesting mixer for the Austin Geocachers Meetup, followed by my friend Reed&#8217;s band, World Racketeering Squad at Headhunters.</p>
<p>Friday = video games.</p>
<p>Come Saturday and SXSW will start to ramp up. While I am not attending the insane industry fame fest proper, I will be checking out peripheral parties and events, like the one put on by io9 and Gawker media. MC Frontalot and Stormtroopers!</p>
<p>Sunday finds me hanging out with friends.</p>
<p>Monday there is a Meetup for all the Meetup organizers hosted by the Meetup bigwigs in town for SXSW. Supposedly we will be discussing strategies. My meetup is awesome, so I&#8217;m not sure what I will take home from it except maybe some beers in my belly.</p>
<p>The rest of the week is a question mark. Chances are I will check out a few SXSW things, but more likely stay at home.</p>
<p>Then there is a big lull the following week right before PAX East. I&#8217;m really looking forward to it. By all accounts, this looks like it will be the geek convention suited for me. I probably won&#8217;t do GenCon again and I&#8217;m not sure I&#8217;ll ever do a ComiCon or E3. But PAX seems like the perfect blend of those things.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.dreampunk.com/2010/03/04/march-marches-on/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inspiration</title>
		<link>http://www.dreampunk.com/2005/08/24/inspiration/</link>
		<comments>http://www.dreampunk.com/2005/08/24/inspiration/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2005 05:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[House of Whack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Music]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://dreampunk.dreynet.com/2005/08/24/inspiration/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Sometimes I wonder why I find myself in certain situations, but then a magical catalyst of environment and circumstance gels together to inspire an idea. Tonight, at the excellent Coldplay concert, I was struck by an idea for House of Whack so brilliant that I impressed myself. I sat on the hillside of the Journal [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sometimes I wonder why I find myself in certain situations, but then a magical catalyst of environment and circumstance gels together to inspire an idea.  Tonight, at the excellent Coldplay concert, I was struck by an idea for <a href="http://www.houseofwhack.net">House of Whack</a> so brilliant that I impressed myself.  I sat on the hillside of the Journal Pavilion, scribbling on my notepad while my muse played on stage, accompanied by some of the best visual effects I had seen at a concert.</p>
<p>In my own playtesting of version 2, I have been surprised at how much better the game is.  I am rarely ecstatic about anything I&#8217;ve made, but I have to say that I&#8217;m feeling pretty clever lately.  Version 2 is very, very good.  But this epiphany I had tonight kicks the dial up to 11.  I&#8217;ve devised something so astonishing and cool.  It will demonstrate the power and flexibility of the Whack system.  Yes, &#8220;system.&#8221;  As in d20, as in GURPS.</p>
<p>On the other hand, I might be the only one interested in this idea at all, but we&#8217;ll see&#8230;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.dreampunk.com/2005/08/24/inspiration/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
