<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	
	>
<channel>
	<title>Comments for DreamPunk Productions</title>
	<atom:link href="http://www.dreampunk.com/comments/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://www.dreampunk.com</link>
	<description>Game and story-shaped designs</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 12:15:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.9</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Comment on The Stork has launched! by Drey</title>
		<link>http://www.dreampunk.com/2011/01/29/the-stork-has-launched/#comment-4</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Drey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 12:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://dreampunk.dreynet.com/2011/01/29/the-stork-has-launched/#comment-4</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Well, I have your cold medicine addled noggin to thank for reminding me to add contact information to the site! I got so wrapped up in the launch of The Stork that I forgot to add that page.

Stork wallpaper can definitely happen. Give me some time to put that together.

Yes, I have considered a Facebook page for The Stork. Originally, I wanted the official Stork site to be the main source of Stork info so I wan&#039;t sure I wanted a Facebook page as well. But it wouldn&#039;t be too hard to set up a Facebook page that pulls the news feed from The Stork site.]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Well, I have your cold medicine addled noggin to thank for reminding me to add contact information to the site! I got so wrapped up in the launch of The Stork that I forgot to add that page.</p>
<p>Stork wallpaper can definitely happen. Give me some time to put that together.</p>
<p>Yes, I have considered a Facebook page for The Stork. Originally, I wanted the official Stork site to be the main source of Stork info so I wan&#8217;t sure I wanted a Facebook page as well. But it wouldn&#8217;t be too hard to set up a Facebook page that pulls the news feed from The Stork site.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Comment on The Stork has launched! by Doctor Checkmate</title>
		<link>http://www.dreampunk.com/2011/01/29/the-stork-has-launched/#comment-3</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Doctor Checkmate]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2011 21:33:24 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://dreampunk.dreynet.com/2011/01/29/the-stork-has-launched/#comment-3</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Just ordered two copies of the Stork from IPR, and I want to tell more people about it. I&#039;m a gamer, a sociologist obsessed with crowd sourcing and flash mobs), and a philosopher (I concentrated my studies in ethics). So, you can imagine, when I discovered the Stork I about exploded!

I am contacting you here because my cold medicine addled noggin won&#039;t allow me to find a proper contact button or email. And, cause I would love a Stork wallpaper. Preferably that looked like the what is the stork website, but the image attached to this post would be excellent, too. The point being, I often have my laptop in a public place and I would love to have people ask me about the wall paper... Maybe something with a pulpy adventure font: &quot;WHAT IS THE STORK?&quot;

Any way, one last thing, have you considered a Facebook page for The Stork?]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Just ordered two copies of the Stork from IPR, and I want to tell more people about it. I&#8217;m a gamer, a sociologist obsessed with crowd sourcing and flash mobs), and a philosopher (I concentrated my studies in ethics). So, you can imagine, when I discovered the Stork I about exploded!</p>
<p>I am contacting you here because my cold medicine addled noggin won&#8217;t allow me to find a proper contact button or email. And, cause I would love a Stork wallpaper. Preferably that looked like the what is the stork website, but the image attached to this post would be excellent, too. The point being, I often have my laptop in a public place and I would love to have people ask me about the wall paper&#8230; Maybe something with a pulpy adventure font: &#8220;WHAT IS THE STORK?&#8221;</p>
<p>Any way, one last thing, have you considered a Facebook page for The Stork?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
